<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ChickenRecipe</string>
    <string name="app_ad_id">vJaaAn75zpHkwzOu5foDfI9Gtw7ST4OMpMFXMJRVyBmPd3R5QNFpmJ0pOip2IDbmg1U5kDxDw94kytDWSmTZP9</string>
    <string name="banner_ad_id">cae754cca1a7655e</string>
    <string name="interstitial_ad_id">cae754cca1a7655e</string>

    <!-- Font -->
    <string name="roboto_regular">sans-serif</string>
    <string name="roboto_light">sans-serif-light</string>
    <string name="roboto_condensed">sans-serif-condensed</string>
    <string name="roboto_thin">sans-serif-thin</string>
    <string name="roboto_medium">sans-serif-medium</string>

    <string name="disclaimer_text">In Android Studio, mediation typically refers to the process of integrating third-party advertising networks or ad platforms into your Android application.\n\nMediation allows you to maximize your app\'s revenue by displaying ads from multiple ad networks, which compete for ad space in your app.\n\nWhen you mediate ads, you can choose from a variety of ad networks and optimize ad delivery based on factors such as ad fill rates, eCPM (effective cost per mille), and user engagement.\n\nBy mediating ads from multiple networks, you can increase your chances of earning revenue from your app. It also provides a way to diversify your ad revenue sources, reducing your dependence on a single ad network.\n\nKeep in mind that the specific implementation details may vary depending on the ad networks you choose and the mediation platform you use, but the general principles of mediation remain consistent.\n\nTo manage the mediation process, you can use a mediation platform like Google AdMob Mediation or a third-party mediation solution.\n\nThese platforms provide a centralized dashboard where you can configure mediation settings, set mediation priorities, and track ad performance.</string>

    <!--    ##########  Low Calories Recipes-->

    <string name="asian_chicken_and_pasta_salad_title">Asian Chicken and Pasta Salad</string>
    <string name="asian_chicken_and_pasta_salad_time">25min</string>
    <string name="asian_chicken_and_pasta_salad_calories">593kcal</string>
    <string name="asian_chicken_and_pasta_salad_fats">27g</string>
    <string name="asian_chicken_and_pasta_salad_proteins">34g</string>
    <string name="asian_chicken_and_pasta_salad_ingredients">•1/4 cup soy sauce\n• 2 tbsp toasted sesame oil\n• 2\-3 Tablespoons white vinegar adjust for taste\n• 1 Tablespoon Rice vinegar\n• 1/4 cup olive oil\n• 1 tbsp brown sugar\n• 12 ounces bow tie pasta about 4 cups\n• 2 cups rotisserie chicken breast meat chopped\n• 1 cup carrot shredded\n• 3/4 cup cilantro roughly chopped\n• 1/2 cup green onion thinly sliced\n• 1/2 cup red bell pepper diced\n• 1/2 cup peanuts chopped fine\n• 1 cup mandarin oranges drained</string>
    <string name="asian_chicken_and_pasta_salad_instruction"><![CDATA[
    <b>Step 1:</b> Mix together dressing ingredients in a bowl and set aside. (Or put in jar, secure lid, and shake to mix).<br/><br/>
    <b>Step 2:</b> Cook bow tie pasta in boiling water, for about 10 minutes or one minute less than package directions indicate, so you get a nice al dente pasta.<br/><br/>
    <b>Step 3:</b> Drain pasta, and rinse with cold water.<br/><br/>
    <b>Step 4:</b> Put rinsed pasta in a large mixing bowl.<br/><br/>
    <b>Step 5:</b> Add chicken, carrots, cilantro, onion, bell pepper, and peanuts, and dressing.<br/><br/>
    <b>Step 6:</b> Toss to coat.<br/><br/>
    <b>Step 7:</b> Add (drained) mandarin oranges at end, and gently stir throughout.<br/><br/>
    <b>Step 8:</b> Serve immediately. Garnish with sesame seeds if desired. And additional green onion.]]></string>

    <string name="greek_potatoes_oven_roasted_and_delicious_title">Chicken Adobo</string>
    <string name="greek_potatoes_oven_roasted_and_delicious_time">35min</string>
    <string name="greek_potatoes_oven_roasted_and_delicious_calories"> 435Kcal</string>
    <string name="greek_potatoes_oven_roasted_and_delicious_fats">14g</string>
    <string name="greek_potatoes_oven_roasted_and_delicious_proteins">8g</string>
    <string name="greek_potatoes_oven_roasted_and_delicious_ingredients">• 2 lbs chicken thighs, bone-in and skin-on\n• 1 cup soy sauce\n• 1 cup white vinegar\n• 1 onion, peeled and sliced thinly\n• 6 cloves garlic, minced\n• 1 teaspoon peppercorns\n• 3 bay leaves\n• 1 tablespoon oil (for cooking)</string>
    <string name="greek_potatoes_oven_roasted_and_delicious_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> In a bowl, combine soy sauce, vinegar, garlic, peppercorns, and bay leaves. Mix well.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Place chicken in a large bowl or ziplock bag and pour in the marinade. Marinate in the refrigerator for at least 30 minutes (overnight for better flavor).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Heat oil in a wide, heavy-bottomed pan over medium heat. Add onions and cook until softened.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Add marinated chicken and cook until brown on all sides.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Pour in the marinade and bring to a boil. Reduce heat, cover, and simmer for about 30-40 minutes or until chicken is tender.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Remove the lid, and continue simmering until the sauce is reduced and thickened.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Serve hot over steamed rice.]]></string>

    <string name="crock_pot_potato_chowder_title">Butter Chicken (Murgh Makhani)</string>
    <string name="crock_pot_potato_chowder_time">40min</string>
    <string name="crock_pot_potato_chowder_calories">500kcal</string>
    <string name="crock_pot_potato_chowder_fats">18g</string>
    <string name="crock_pot_potato_chowder_proteins">9g</string>
    <string name="crock_pot_potato_chowder_ingredients">• 1.5 lbs boneless, skinless chicken thighs, cut into bite-sized pieces\n• 1 cup plain yogurt\n• 1 tablespoon ginger-garlic paste\n• 1 teaspoon red chili powder\n• 1 teaspoon turmeric powder\n• 1 teaspoon garam masala\n• 1 teaspoon ground cumin\n• Salt to taste\n• 2 tablespoons vegetable oil\n• 2 tablespoons butter\n• 1 large onion, finely chopped\n• 1 cup tomato puree\n• 1/2 cup heavy cream\n• 1 teaspoon kasuri methi (dried fenugreek leaves)\n• Fresh cilantro for garnish</string>
    <string name="crock_pot_potato_chowder_instructions"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> In a bowl, mix yogurt with ginger-garlic paste, red chili powder, turmeric powder, garam masala, ground cumin, and salt. Marinate the chicken in this mixture for at least 2 hours, or overnight for best results.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Heat oil in a pan over medium-high heat. Add marinated chicken and cook until browned on all sides. Remove the chicken from the pan and set aside.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> In the same pan, add butter and sauté chopped onions until golden brown.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Add tomato puree and cook until the oil separates from the masala.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Return the cooked chicken to the pan, stirring to coat it in the tomato mixture.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Pour in the heavy cream and simmer for 10-15 minutes until the chicken is cooked through and the sauce has thickened.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Crush kasuri methi between your palms and sprinkle it over the chicken. Stir well.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Garnish with fresh cilantro before serving.]]></string>

    <string name="easy_baked_potato_wedges_title">Indian Chicken Curry </string>
    <string name="easy_baked_potato_wedges_time">1hr 30min</string>
    <string name="easy_baked_potato_wedges_calories">370kcal</string>
    <string name="easy_baked_potato_wedges_fats">15g</string>
    <string name="easy_baked_potato_wedges_proteins">9g</string>
    <string name="easy_baked_potato_wedges_ingredients">• 1.5 lbs chicken, cut into pieces (bone-in for added flavor)\n• 2 large onions, finely chopped\n• 2 tomatoes, pureed\n• 1/4 cup vegetable oil or ghee\n• 1/2 cup plain yogurt\n• 1 tablespoon ginger-garlic paste\n• 1 teaspoon turmeric powder\n• 1 teaspoon chili powder (adjust to taste)\n• 1 teaspoon ground coriander\n• 1 teaspoon ground cumin\n• 1/2 teaspoon garam masala\n• Salt to taste\n• Fresh cilantro for garnish</string>
    <string name="easy_baked_potato_wedges_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> In a large pot, heat oil or ghee over medium heat. Add chopped onions and sauté until golden brown.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Add ginger-garlic paste and cook for a minute until the raw smell disappears.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Add turmeric powder, chili powder, ground coriander, ground cumin, and salt. Stir well to combine.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Add chicken pieces and cook until they are browned on all sides.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Add yogurt and mix well, ensuring the chicken is coated with the yogurt-spice mixture.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Pour in the tomato puree and cook until the oil starts to separate from the masala.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Add water as needed to achieve your desired consistency. Cover and simmer until the chicken is cooked through, and the flavors meld together (usually around 30-40 minutes).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Sprinkle garam masala and garnish with fresh cilantro before serving.]]></string>

    <string name="potato_soup_title">Sweet and Sour Chicken:</string>
    <string name="potato_soup_time">45min</string>
    <string name="potato_soup_calories">520kcal</string>
    <string name="potato_soup_fats">27g</string>
    <string name="potato_soup_proteins">3g</string>
    <string name="potato_soup_ingredients">• For the Chicken:\n• 1.5 lbs boneless, skinless chicken breasts, cut into bite-sized pieces\n• 1 cup cornstarch\n• 2 eggs, beaten\n• Salt and pepper to taste\n• Vegetable oil for frying\n 1/2 For the Sweet and Sour Sauce:\n• 1 cup pineapple juice\n• 1/2 cup ketchup\n• 1/4 cup rice vinegar\n• 1/4 cup soy sauce\n• 1 cup sugar\n• 1/4 cup cornstarch (dissolved in 1/4 cup water)\n• 1 bell pepper, cut into chunks\n• 1 cup pineapple chunks (fresh or canned)</string>
    <string name="potato_soup_instruction"><![CDATA[
    For the Chicken:
        <b>Step 1:</b> Season the chicken pieces with salt and pepper.<br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Dip each chicken piece into beaten eggs and then coat with cornstarch, ensuring an even coating.<br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Heat vegetable oil in a pan over medium-high heat. Fry the chicken until golden brown and cooked through. Remove and set aside on paper towels to drain excess oil.<br/>
    For the Sweet and Sour Sauce:
        <b>Step 1:</b> In a separate saucepan, combine pineapple juice, ketchup, rice vinegar, soy sauce, and sugar. Bring to a simmer over medium heat.<br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Add the dissolved cornstarch to the sauce, stirring continuously until it thickens.<br/>
         <b>Step 2:</b> Add bell peppers and pineapple chunks to the sauce. Simmer for an additional 2-3 minutes until the vegetables are slightly tender.<br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Combine the fried chicken with the sweet and sour sauce, ensuring the chicken pieces are well-coated.]]></string>

    <string name="slow_cooker_cheesy_chicken_penne_title">Chicken Teriyaki</string>
    <string name="slow_cooker_cheesy_chicken_penne_time">35min</string>
    <string name="slow_cooker_cheesy_chicken_penne_calories">420kcal</string>
    <string name="slow_cooker_cheesy_chicken_penne_fats">23g </string>
    <string name="slow_cooker_cheesy_chicken_penne_proteins">36g</string>
    <string name="slow_cooker_cheesy_chicken_penne_ingredients">• 1.5 lbs boneless, skinless chicken thighs, cut into bite-sized pieces\n• 1/2 cup soy sauce\n• 1/4 cup mirin (sweet rice wine)\n• 1/4 cup sake (Japanese rice wine) or dry white wine\n• 3 tablespoons brown sugar\n• 1 tablespoon honey\n• 1 tablespoon grated fresh ginger\n• 2 cloves garlic, minced\n• 2 tablespoons vegetable oil\n• Sesame seeds and chopped green onions for garnish</string>
    <string name="slow_cooker_cheesy_chicken_penne_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> In a bowl, combine soy sauce, mirin, sake, brown sugar, honey, grated ginger, and minced garlic. Mix well to create the teriyaki sauce.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Place chicken pieces in a ziplock bag or shallow dish and pour half of the teriyaki sauce over them. Marinate for at least 30 minutes, or preferably 2 hours in the refrigerator.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Heat vegetable oil in a pan over medium-high heat. Remove chicken from the marinade, allowing excess to drip off, and cook until browned on all sides and cooked through.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Pour the remaining teriyaki sauce into the pan with the cooked chicken. Simmer until the sauce thickens and glazes the chicken.<br/><br/>
       <b>Step 5:</b> Garnish with sesame seeds and chopped green onions before serving.]]></string>

    <string name="crock_pot_chicken_taco_meat_title">Shanghai Chicken Stir-Fry</string>
    <string name="crock_pot_chicken_taco_meat_time">40min</string>
    <string name="crock_pot_chicken_taco_meat_calories">290kcal</string>
    <string name="crock_pot_chicken_taco_meat_fats">2g</string>
    <string name="crock_pot_chicken_taco_meat_proteins">17g</string>
    <string name="crock_pot_chicken_taco_meat_ingredients">• 1.5 lbs boneless, skinless chicken breasts, thinly sliced\n• 12 tablespoons soy sauce,1 tablespoon oyster sauce,1 tablespoon hoisin sauce\n• 1 tablespoon Shaoxing wine (Chinese cooking wine) or dry sherry\n• 1 teaspoon cornstarch,2 tablespoons vegetable oil,1 tablespoon ginger, minced\n• 2 cloves garlic, minced,1 cup shiitake mushrooms, sliced,1 cup broccoli florets\n• 1 red bell pepper, thinly sliced,1 carrot, julienned,2 green onions, sliced \n• Sesame seeds for garnish (optional),1 cup snow peas, ends trimmed</string>
    <string name="crock_pot_chicken_taco_meat_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> In a bowl, mix soy sauce, oyster sauce, hoisin sauce, Shaoxing wine, and cornstarch. Add sliced chicken and marinate for at least 15-30 minutes.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Heat vegetable oil in a wok or large pan over high heat. Add minced ginger and garlic, stir-frying for about 30 seconds.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Add marinated chicken to the wok and stir-fry until browned and cooked through. Remove the chicken from the wok and set aside.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> In the same wok, add a bit more oil if needed. Stir-fry mushrooms, broccoli, bell pepper, carrot, and snow peas until they are crisp-tender.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Return the cooked chicken to the wok, add green onions, and toss everything together until well combined and heated through.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Garnish with sesame seeds if desired.]]></string>

    <string name="mahogany_beef_stew_title">Hainanese Chicken Rice</string>
    <string name="mahogany_beef_stew_time">1hr 20min</string>
    <string name="mahogany_beef_stew_calories">475kcal</string>
    <string name="mahogany_beef_stew_fats">26g</string>
    <string name="mahogany_beef_stew_proteins">62g</string>
    <string name="mahogany_beef_stew_ingredients"> \n• 1 whole chicken (about 3-4 lbs)\n• 1 tablespoon sesame oil,2 tablespoons soy sauce,1 tablespoon oyster sauce\n• 2 stalks green onions, cut into halves,2 slices ginger\n• Salt to taste\n• 2 cups jasmine rice,4 cups chicken broth (from cooking the chicken)\n• 2 slices ginger,2 cloves garlic, minced\n• 1 pandan leaf (optional, for fragrance),Salt to taste\n• 2 tablespoons soy sauce\n• 1 tablespoon oyster sauce\n• 1 tablespoon sesame oil\n• 1 clove garlic, minced\n• 1 tablespoon cilantro, finely chopped,1 tablespoon ginger, minced</string>
    <string name="mahogany_beef_stew_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Rinse the chicken inside and out. Rub with salt and rinse again.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> In a large pot, bring water to a boil. Add ginger, green onions, sesame oil, soy sauce, and oyster sauce.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Gently lower the chicken into the pot, ensuring it\'s fully submerged. Cook for about 40-50 minutes or until the chicken is cooked through.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Remove the chicken and plunge it into ice water for a few minutes to stop the cooking process. Rub the chicken with sesame oil.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Rinse the rice under cold water until the water runs clear.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> In a pot, heat a bit of oil and sauté garlic and ginger until fragrant.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Add the rice and stir to coat with the aromatic oil.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Add chicken broth, pandan leaf, and salt. Bring to a boil, then reduce heat, cover, and simmer until the rice is cooked.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Mix soy sauce, oyster sauce, sesame oil, minced garlic, minced ginger, and chopped cilantro.]]></string>

    <string name="chili_con_carne_title">Cashew Chicken</string>
    <string name="chili_con_carne_time">1hr 15min</string>
    <string name="chili_con_carne_calories">680kcal</string>
    <string name="chili_con_carne_fats">32g</string>
    <string name="chili_con_carne_proteins">53f</string>
    <string name="chili_con_carne_ingredients">• 1.5 lbs boneless, skinless chicken breasts, cut into bite-sized pieces\n• 1 cup unsalted cashews\n• 1 cup broccoli florets\n• 1 red bell pepper, sliced\n• 1 cup snow peas, ends trimmed\n• 3 tablespoons soy sauce\n• 1 tablespoon oyster sauce\n• 1 tablespoon hoisin sauce\n• 1 tablespoon cornstarch\n• 2 tablespoons vegetable oil\n• 3 cloves garlic, minced\n• 1 tablespoon fresh ginger, grated\n• 1 teaspoon sesame oil\n• Green onions, sliced for garnish\n• Cooked white rice for serving</string>
    <string name="chili_con_carne_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> In a bowl, mix soy sauce, oyster sauce, hoisin sauce, and cornstarch. Add the chicken pieces and let them marinate for at least 15-30 minutes.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Heat vegetable oil in a wok or large skillet over medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Add minced garlic and grated ginger, stir-frying for about 30 seconds until fragrant.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Add the marinated chicken to the wok and stir-fry until browned and cooked through.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Add broccoli, red bell pepper, and snow peas to the wok. Stir-fry for an additional 3-5 minutes until the vegetables are crisp-tender.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Add the cashews and sesame oil to the wok, tossing everything together.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Garnish with sliced green onions before serving. Enjoy!]]></string>

    <string name="german_potato_salad_title">Sesame Chicken</string>
    <string name="german_potato_salad_time">40min</string>
    <string name="german_potato_salad_calories">520kcal</string>
    <string name="german_potato_salad_fats">5g</string>
    <string name="german_potato_salad_proteins">7g</string>
    <string name="german_potato_salad_ingredients">• 1.5 lbs boneless, skinless chicken thighs or breasts, cut into bite-sized pieces\n• 1 cup cornstarch\n• 2 eggs, beaten\n• Salt and pepper to taste\n• Vegetable oil for frying\n• 1/4 cup soy sauce\n• 2 tablespoons honey\n• 2 tablespoons hoisin sauce\n• 1 tablespoon rice vinegar\n• 1 teaspoon sesame oil\n• 2 cloves garlic, minced\n• 1 tablespoon ginger, grated\n• 1 tablespoon cornstarch (dissolved in 2 tablespoons water)\n• Sesame seeds\n• Green onions, sliced</string>
    <string name="german_potato_salad_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Season chicken pieces with salt and pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Dredge each piece in beaten eggs and then coat with cornstarch, ensuring an even coating.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Heat vegetable oil in a pan over medium-high heat. Fry chicken until golden brown and cooked through. Drain on paper towels.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> In a small bowl, mix soy sauce, honey, hoisin sauce, rice vinegar, sesame oil, minced garlic, and grated ginger.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> In a separate saucepan, heat the sauce mixture over medium heat. Once it starts to simmer, add the cornstarch mixture and stir until the sauce thickens.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Toss the fried chicken in the sesame sauce until well-coated.<br/><br/>

        <b>Step 7:</b> Garnish with sesame seeds and sliced green onions. Enjoy!]]></string>

    <string name="german_cucumber_salad_title">Chinese Chicken Wings</string>
    <string name="german_cucumber_salad_time">3hr</string>
    <string name="german_cucumber_salad_calories">455kcal</string>
    <string name="german_cucumber_salad_fats">3</string>
    <string name="german_cucumber_salad_proteins">5</string>
    <string name="german_cucumber_salad_ingredients">• 2 lbs chicken wings, split at joints, tips discarded\n• 2 tablespoons soy sauce\n• 2 tablespoons hoisin sauce\n• 2 tablespoons oyster sauce\n• 1 tablespoon honey\n• 1 tablespoon sesame oil\n• 2 cloves garlic, minced\n• 1 tablespoon ginger, grated\n• 1 tablespoon rice vinegar\n• 1 teaspoon Chinese five-spice powder\n• 1 tablespoon vegetable oil\n• Sesame seeds and chopped green onions for garnish</string>
    <string name="german_cucumber_salad_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Preheat the oven to 400°F (200°C).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> In a bowl, mix soy sauce, hoisin sauce, oyster sauce, honey, sesame oil, minced garlic, grated ginger, rice vinegar, and Chinese five-spice powder to create a marinade.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Place the chicken wings in a large ziplock bag or a bowl and pour the marinade over them. Ensure the wings are fully coated. Marinate for at least 30 minutes, or preferably 2 hours in the refrigerator.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Line a baking sheet with parchment paper. Place a wire rack on top.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Arrange the marinated chicken wings on the wire rack, allowing excess marinade to drip off.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Bake in the preheated oven for about 40-45 minutes, turning the wings halfway through, until they are golden brown and cooked through.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> In a small saucepan, heat vegetable oil over medium heat. Add any remaining marinade and simmer until it thickens into a glaze.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Brush the glaze over the baked chicken wings and broil for an additional 3-5 minutes until they are caramelized.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Garnish with sesame seeds and chopped green onions before serving.]]></string>

    <string name="german_tomato_salad_title">Shanghai Chicken Stir-Fry</string>
    <string name="german_tomato_salad_time">40min</string>
    <string name="german_tomato_salad_calories">385kcal</string>
    <string name="german_tomato_salad_fats">3</string>
    <string name="german_tomato_salad_proteins">5</string>
    <string name="german_tomato_salad_ingredients">• 1.5 lbs boneless, skinless chicken breasts, thinly sliced\n• 2 tablespoons soy sauce\n• 1 tablespoon oyster sauce\n• 1 tablespoon hoisin sauce\n• 1 tablespoon Shaoxing wine (Chinese cooking wine) or dry sherry\n• 1 teaspoon cornstarch\n• 2 tablespoons vegetable oil\n• 1 tablespoon ginger, minced\n• 2 cloves garlic, minced\n• 1 cup shiitake mushrooms, sliced\n• 1 cup broccoli florets\n• 1 red bell pepper, thinly sliced\n• 1 carrot, julienned\n• 1 cup snow peas, ends trimmed\n• 2 green onions, sliced\n• Sesame seeds for garnish (optional)</string>
    <string name="german_tomato_salad_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> In a bowl, mix soy sauce, oyster sauce, hoisin sauce, Shaoxing wine, and cornstarch. Add sliced chicken and let it marinate for at least 15-30 minutes.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Heat vegetable oil in a wok or large skillet over medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Add minced ginger and garlic to the wok, stir-frying for about 30 seconds until fragrant.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Add the marinated chicken to the wok and stir-fry until browned and cooked through. Remove the chicken from the wok and set aside.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> In the same wok, add a bit more oil if needed. Stir-fry shiitake mushrooms, broccoli, red bell pepper, carrot, and snow peas until they are crisp-tender.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Return the cooked chicken to the wok, add green onions, and toss everything together until well combined and heated through.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Garnish with sesame seeds if desired.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Serve this Shanghai Chicken Stir-Fry over steamed rice or noodles for a quick and flavorful Asian-inspired meal. Enjoy!]]></string>


    <!--    ##########  Low Vegan Recipes-->

    <string name="tempeh_chicken_salad_title">Saudi Chicken Kofta</string>
    <string name="tempeh_chicken_salad_time">40min</string>
    <string name="tempeh_chicken_salad_calories">375kcal</string>
    <string name="tempeh_chicken_salad_fats">32g</string>
    <string name="tempeh_chicken_salad_proteins">17g</string>
    <string name="tempeh_chicken_salad_ingredients">• 1 lb ground chicken\n• 1 small onion, finely grated\n• 2 cloves garlic, minced\n• 2 tablespoons fresh parsley, finely chopped\n• 1 teaspoon ground cumin\n• 1 teaspoon ground coriander\n• 1 teaspoon ground paprika\n• 1/2 teaspoon ground cinnamon\n• Salt and pepper to taste\n• 2 tablespoons vegetable oil (for grilling)\n• 1/2 cup tahini\n• 2 tablespoons lemon juice\n• 2 cloves garlic, minced\n• Salt to taste\n• Water (as needed to adjust consistency)</string>
    <string name="tempeh_chicken_salad_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> In a large bowl, mix ground chicken, grated onion, minced garlic, chopped parsley, ground cumin, ground coriander, ground paprika, ground cinnamon, salt, and pepper. Combine well.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Shape the mixture into small, elongated kofta (sausage) shapes.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Preheat a grill or grill pan over medium-high heat. Brush the kofta with vegetable oil.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Grill the chicken kofta for about 10-15 minutes, turning occasionally, until they are cooked through and have a nice char.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> In a bowl, whisk together tahini, lemon juice, minced garlic, and salt.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Gradually add water while whisking until the sauce reaches your desired consistency.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Adjust seasoning if needed.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b>Saudi Chicken Kofta is often served with rice, flatbread, or a side salad. Enjoy this flavorful Arabian dish! ]]></string>

    <string name="white_bean_pumpkin_soup_title">Arabic Chicken Mandi</string>
    <string name="white_bean_pumpkin_soup_time">2hr</string>
    <string name="white_bean_pumpkin_soup_calories">525kcal</string>
    <string name="white_bean_pumpkin_soup_fats">6</string>
    <string name="white_bean_pumpkin_soup_proteins">8</string>
    <string name="white_bean_pumpkin_soup_ingredients">• 1 whole chicken (about 3-4 lbs), cleaned and cut into pieces\n• 2 cups basmati rice, washed and soaked\n• 1 large onion, finely chopped\n• 4 cloves garlic, minced\n• 2 tablespoons mandi spice mix (a blend of cumin, coriander, black lime, cinnamon, cardamom, cloves)\n• 1 teaspoon ground turmeric\n• 1 teaspoon ground black lime (loomi) or substitute with lime zest\n• 1 teaspoon ground cumin\n• Salt to taste\n• 2 tablespoons vegetable oil\n• 3 cups chicken broth\n• 1/4 cup ghee or clarified butter\n• 1/4 cup raisins (optional)</string>
    <string name="white_bean_pumpkin_soup_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> In a bowl, mix mandi spice mix, ground turmeric, ground black lime (loomi), ground cumin, salt, and vegetable oil to create a marinade.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Rub the chicken pieces with the spice marinade, ensuring they are well-coated. Let it marinate for at least 2 hours, or preferably overnight in the refrigerator.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Preheat the oven to 375°F (190°C).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> In a large oven-safe pot, heat a bit of vegetable oil. Sauté chopped onions and minced garlic until softened.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Add the marinated chicken pieces to the pot and brown them on all sides.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Pour in enough water to cover the chicken. Cover the pot and let it simmer until the chicken is cooked through.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Rinse the soaked basmati rice under cold water until the water runs clear.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> In a separate pot, bring chicken broth to a boil. Add ghee and salt to taste.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Add the rinsed rice to the boiling broth. Reduce the heat to low, cover, and let it simmer until the rice is cooked and the liquid is absorbed.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Arabic Chicken Mandi is traditionally served with a side of yogurt or a tomato-based sauce. Enjoy this aromatic and flavorful Arabian dish!]]></string>

    <string name="heather_stir_fry_sauce_title">Dajaj Mahshi (Stuffed Chicken)</string>
    <string name="heather_stir_fry_sauce_time">2hr</string>
    <string name="heather_stir_fry_sauce_calories">370kcal</string>
    <string name="heather_stir_fry_sauce_fats">2g</string>
    <string name="heather_stir_fry_sauce_proteins">1.4</string>
    <string name="heather_stir_fry_sauce_ingredients">• 1 whole chicken (about 3-4 lbs), cleaned and patted dry\n• 2 cups basmati rice, washed and soaked\n• 1 large onion, finely chopped\n• 3 tablespoons butter or ghee\n• 1/4 cup pine nuts\n• 1 teaspoon ground cinnamon\n• 1 teaspoon ground allspice\n• Salt and pepper to taste\n• Vegetable oil for brushing\n• Chicken giblets (optional)\n• 1 onion, quartered2 carrots, peeled and chopped\n• 2 celery stalks, chopped\n• 1 bay leaf\n• Salt and pepper to taste</string>
    <string name="heather_stir_fry_sauce_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> In a pan, sauté chopped onions in butter or ghee until softened.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Add pine nuts and continue to sauté until the nuts are golden brown.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Mix in soaked basmati rice, ground cinnamon, ground allspice, salt, and pepper. Cook for a few minutes until the rice is coated with the spices.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Stuff the whole chicken with the prepared rice mixture.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Truss the chicken to secure the stuffing inside.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Preheat the oven to 375°F (190°C).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Brush the chicken with vegetable oil and place it in a roasting pan.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Roast the chicken in the preheated oven for about 1.5 to 2 hours or until the internal temperature reaches 165°F (74°C).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> In a large pot, combine chicken giblets (if using), quartered onion, chopped carrots, chopped celery, bay leaf, salt, and pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Add enough water to cover the ingredients and bring the pot to a boil.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 11:</b> Simmer the broth for at least 30-45 minutes to develop flavor.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 12:</b> Strain the broth and keep it warm.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 13:</b> Carve the stuffed chicken and serve it over a bed of cooked rice.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 14:</b> Drizzle the chicken with some of the prepared chicken broth.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 15:</b> Garnish with chopped parsley if desired.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 16:</b> Enjoy this traditional Arabian stuffed chicken dish!]]></string>

    <string name="kale_chips_title">Arabic Chicken Biryani</string>
    <string name="kale_chips_time">1.5hr</string>
    <string name="kale_chips_calories">325kcal</string>
    <string name="kale_chips_fats">5g</string>
    <string name="kale_chips_proteins">2g</string>
    <string name="kale_chips_ingredients">• 1.5 lbs chicken, cut into pieces\n• 1 cup yogurt\n• 2 tablespoons Arabic spice blend (cumin, coriander, paprika, cinnamon, cloves)\n• 3 tablespoons vegetable oil\n• 1 large onion, thinly sliced\n• 2 tomatoes, chopped\n• 3 cloves garlic, minced\n• 1 tablespoon ginger, grated\n• Salt and pepper to taste\n• Fresh cilantro and mint for garnish\n• 2 cups basmati rice, washed and soaked\n• 4 cups chicken broth\n• 1 bay leaf\n• 4 cardamom pods\n• 4 cloves\n• 1 cinnamon stick\n• 2 tablespoons ghee or clarified butter</string>
    <string name="kale_chips_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> In a bowl, marinate the chicken pieces with yogurt, Arabic spice blend, salt, and pepper. Let it marinate for at least 30 minutes.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> In a large pot, heat vegetable oil and sauté thinly sliced onions until golden brown.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Add minced garlic and grated ginger, sautéing until fragrant.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Add marinated chicken and cook until it\'s browned on all sides.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Stir in chopped tomatoes and cook until they are softened.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> In a separate pot, bring chicken broth to a boil. Add washed and soaked basmati rice, bay leaf, cardamom pods, cloves, cinnamon stick, and ghee.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> In a large oven-safe dish, layer the partially cooked rice over the chicken.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Cover the dish tightly with aluminum foil and bake in a preheated oven at 350°F (180°C) for about 30-40 minutes or until the chicken is fully cooked, and the rice is tender.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Garnish the Arabic Chicken Biryani with fried onions, toasted almonds, cashews, fresh cilantro, and mint.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Serve hot, and enjoy!]]></string>

    <string name="cucumber_tomato_salad_title">Jerk Chicken Arabic Style</string>
    <string name="cucumber_tomato_salad_time">2hr</string>
    <string name="cucumber_tomato_salad_calories">720kcal</string>
    <string name="cucumber_tomato_salad_fats">5g</string>
    <string name="cucumber_tomato_salad_proteins">2g</string>
    <string name="cucumber_tomato_salad_ingredients">• 2 lbs chicken pieces (thighs, drumsticks, or wings)\n• 1 large onion, chopped\n• 3 cloves garlic, minced\n• 1 tablespoon ginger, grated\n• 2 tablespoons olive oil\n• 2 tablespoons soy sauce\n• 1 tablespoon honey\n• 1 tablespoon ground allspice\n• 1 teaspoon ground cinnamon\n• 1 teaspoon ground cumin\n• 1 teaspoon smoked paprika\n• 1 teaspoon dried thyme\n• 1 teaspoon cayenne pepper (adjust to taste)\n• Salt and pepper to taste\Juice of 2 limes\n• 1 cup Greek yogurt\n• 1 tablespoon tahini1 tablespoon lemon juice\n• 1 clove garlic, minced\n• Salt and pepper to taste</string>
    <string name="cucumber_tomato_salad_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> In a blender or food processor, combine chopped onion, minced garlic, grated ginger, olive oil, soy sauce, honey, allspice, cinnamon, cumin, smoked paprika, dried thyme, cayenne pepper, salt, pepper, and lime juice. Blend until smooth.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Place the chicken pieces in a large bowl or a ziplock bag. Pour the jerk marinade over the chicken, ensuring each piece is well-coated. Marinate for at least 2 hours, or preferably overnight in the refrigerator.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Preheat the grill or oven to medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Grill the chicken for about 20-25 minutes, turning occasionally, until the chicken is fully cooked and has a nice char. Alternatively, you can bake the chicken in the oven at 375°F (190°C) for approximately 30-35 minutes.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> In a bowl, mix Greek yogurt, tahini, lemon juice, minced garlic, salt, and pepper. Adjust the seasoning to taste.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Serve the Jerk Chicken with the yogurt sauce on the side.]]></string>

    <string name="garden_vegetable_soup_title">Makloubeh Chicken</string>
    <string name="garden_vegetable_soup_time">1hr 25min</string>
    <string name="garden_vegetable_soup_calories">655kcal</string>
    <string name="garden_vegetable_soup_fats">12g</string>
    <string name="garden_vegetable_soup_proteins">6g</string>
    <string name="garden_vegetable_soup_ingredients">• 2 cups basmati rice, washed and soaked\n• 1 whole chicken (about 3-4 lbs), cut into pieces\n• 1 large eggplant, sliced\n• 2 large carrots, peeled and sliced\n• 1 large cauliflower, cut into florets\n• 1 large onion, thinly sliced\n• 4 cloves garlic, minced\n• 1/4 cup vegetable oil\n• 1 teaspoon ground cinnamon\n• 1 teaspoon ground allspice\n• 1 teaspoon ground turmeric\n• Salt and pepper to taste\n• 4 cups chicken broth\n• Chopped fresh parsley for garnish</string>
    <string name="garden_vegetable_soup_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Preheat the oven to 375°F (190°C).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> In a large pot, heat vegetable oil over medium heat. Sauté the sliced onions until they become translucent.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Add minced garlic and continue sautéing until fragrant.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Arrange the chicken pieces in the pot and brown them on all sides.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Sprinkle ground cinnamon, ground allspice, ground turmeric, salt, and pepper over the chicken. Mix well to coat the chicken with the spices.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Add chicken broth to the pot, bring to a boil, then reduce the heat and let it simmer for about 10 minutes.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> While the broth is simmering, arrange sliced eggplants, carrots, and cauliflower in the pot over the chicken.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Add the soaked basmati rice on top of the vegetables, spreading it evenly.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Pour the remaining chicken broth over the rice.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Cover the pot tightly and transfer it to the preheated oven. Bake for approximately 45-60 minutes or until the chicken is fully cooked and the rice is tender.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 11:</b> Carefully invert the pot onto a large serving platter, allowing the rice and vegetables to form a beautiful layered presentation.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 12:</b> Garnish with chopped fresh parsley.]]></string>

    <string name="roasted_root_vegetable_title">Authentic Chicken Parmesan</string>
    <string name="roasted_root_vegetable_time">1hr 20min</string>
    <string name="roasted_root_vegetable_calories">465kcal</string>
    <string name="roasted_root_vegetable_fats">10g</string>
    <string name="roasted_root_vegetable_proteins">4g</string>
    <string name="roasted_root_vegetable_ingredients">• 4 boneless, skinless chicken breasts\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1 cup all-purpose flour, for dredging\n• 2 large eggs\n• 2 cups Italian-style breadcrumbs\n• 1 cup grated Parmesan cheese\n• Olive oil for frying\n• 2 tablespoons olive oil\n• 1 onion, finely chopped\n• 2 cloves garlic, minced\n• 1 can (28 oz) crushed tomatoes\n• 1 teaspoon dried oregano\n• 1 teaspoon dried basil\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1/2 teaspoon sugar (optional, to balance acidity)\n• 1 1/2 cups shredded mozzarella cheese\n• 1/2 cup grated Parmesan cheese\n• Fresh basil or parsley for garnish (optional)</string>
    <string name="roasted_root_vegetable_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> In a saucepan, heat olive oil over medium heat. Add chopped onion and sauté until softened.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Add minced garlic and cook until fragrant.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Pour in crushed tomatoes and add dried oregano, dried basil, salt, and pepper. If the sauce is too acidic, add sugar to balance the flavors.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Simmer the sauce on low heat for about 20-30 minutes, stirring occasionally.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Preheat the oven to 400°F (200°C).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Season chicken breasts with salt and pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Dredge each chicken breast in flour, dip in beaten eggs, and coat with a mixture of breadcrumbs and grated Parmesan.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> In a large skillet, heat olive oil over medium-high heat. Fry the chicken breasts until golden brown on both sides. Transfer to a paper towel to drain excess oil.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> In a baking dish, spread a thin layer of tomato sauce.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Place the fried chicken breasts on top of the sauce.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 11:</b> Spoon more tomato sauce over each chicken breast.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 12:</b> Sprinkle shredded mozzarella and grated Parmesan over the chicken.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 13:</b> Bake in the preheated oven for about 20-25 minutes or until the cheese is melted and bubbly.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 14:</b> Optionally, broil for a couple of minutes until the cheese is golden brown.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 15:</b> Garnish with fresh basil or parsley before serving.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 16:</b> Serve Chicken Parmesan over cooked spaghetti or your favorite pasta.]]></string>

    <string name="roasted_green_beans_title">Persian Slow-Cooked Chicken</string>
    <string name="roasted_green_beans_time">6hr 30min</string>
    <string name="roasted_green_beans_calories">960kcal</string>
    <string name="roasted_green_beans_fats">7g</string>
    <string name="roasted_green_beans_proteins">3g</string>
    <string name="roasted_green_beans_ingredients">• 2 lbs chicken pieces (thighs, drumsticks, or a mix)\n• 1 large onion, finely chopped\n• 3 cloves garlic, minced\n• 2 tablespoons vegetable oil\n• 1 teaspoon ground turmeric\n• 1 teaspoon ground cinnamon\n• 1 teaspoon ground cumin\n• 1 teaspoon ground coriander\n• 1/2 teaspoon ground cardamom\n• Salt and pepper to taste\n• 1 cup chicken broth\n• 1 cup dried apricots, chopped\n• 1 cup pitted prunes, chopped\n• 1/4 cup slivered almonds, toasted (for garnish)\n• Fresh cilantro or parsley for garnish</string>
    <string name="roasted_green_beans_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> In a large skillet, heat vegetable oil over medium heat. Sauté chopped onions until translucent.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Add minced garlic and continue to sauté until fragrant.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Add chicken pieces to the skillet and brown them on all sides.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Sprinkle ground turmeric, ground cinnamon, ground cumin, ground coriander, ground cardamom, salt, and pepper over the chicken. Mix well to coat the chicken with the spices.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Transfer the spiced chicken to a slow cooker.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Pour chicken broth over the chicken in the slow cooker.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Add chopped dried apricots and prunes to the slow cooker.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Set the slow cooker to low heat and cook for 6-8 hours or until the chicken is tender and falls off the bone.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Before serving, toast slivered almonds in a dry pan over medium heat until golden brown.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Garnish the slow-cooked chicken with toasted almonds and fresh cilantro or parsley.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 11:</b> Persian Slow-Cooked Chicken is traditionally served over steamed basmati rice or couscous. Enjoy!]]></string>

    <string name="vegan_almond_biscotti_title">Trinidad Stewed Chicken</string>
    <string name="vegan_almond_biscotti_time">1hr</string>
    <string name="vegan_almond_biscotti_calories">150kcal</string>
    <string name="vegan_almond_biscotti_fats">8g</string>
    <string name="vegan_almond_biscotti_proteins">3g</string>
    <string name="vegan_almond_biscotti_ingredients">• 2 lbs chicken pieces (thighs, drumsticks, or a mix)\n• 2 tablespoons vegetable oil\n• 1 onion, finely chopped\n• 3 cloves garlic, minced\n• 1 bell pepper, diced\n• 2 tomatoes, chopped\n• 1 tablespoon Trinidad curry powder\n• 1 teaspoon ground cumin\n• 1 teaspoon paprika\n• 1/2 teaspoon thyme\n• 2 bay leaves\n• Salt and pepper to taste\n• 1 cup chicken broth\n• 1 cup coconut milk\n• 2 potatoes, peeled and diced\n• Fresh cilantro or parsley for garnish</string>
    <string name="vegan_almond_biscotti_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> In a large pot or Dutch oven, heat vegetable oil over medium heat. Sauté chopped onions until translucent.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Add minced garlic and diced bell pepper, continuing to sauté until softened.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Add chicken pieces to the pot and brown them on all sides.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Sprinkle Trinidad curry powder, ground cumin, paprika, thyme, bay leaves, salt, and pepper over the chicken. Mix well to coat the chicken with the spices.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Add chopped tomatoes to the pot and cook until they break down and release their juices.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Pour in chicken broth and coconut milk. Stir to combine.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Add diced potatoes to the pot and bring the mixture to a simmer.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Cover the pot and let it simmer for about 30-40 minutes or until the chicken is cooked through, and the potatoes are tender.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Adjust salt and pepper to taste.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Garnish with fresh cilantro or parsley before serving.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 11:</b> Serve: Trinidad Stewed Chicken is often served with rice, roti, or bread.]]></string>

    <string name="easy_vegan_pancakes_title">Ultimate Roast Chicken</string>
    <string name="easy_vegan_pancakes_time">2hr 40min</string>
    <string name="easy_vegan_pancakes_calories">380kcal</string>
    <string name="easy_vegan_pancakes_fats">12g</string>
    <string name="easy_vegan_pancakes_proteins">9g</string>
    <string name="easy_vegan_pancakes_ingredients">• 1 whole chicken (about 4-5 lbs), giblets removed\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 2 tablespoons olive oil or melted butter\n• 1 lemon, halved\n• 4-6 garlic cloves, crushed\n• 2 sprigs fresh rosemary (or 1 tablespoon dried rosemary)\n• 1 tablespoon fresh thyme leaves (or 1 teaspoon dried thyme)\n• 1 teaspoon paprika\n• 1 teaspoon garlic powder\n• 1 teaspoon onion powder\n• 1/2 teaspoon dried oregano\n• 1/2 teaspoon dried sage\n• 1/2 teaspoon dried marjoram\n• 1/2 teaspoon dried tarragon (optional)\n• 1/2 cup chicken broth or white wine (for basting)</string>
    <string name="easy_vegan_pancakes_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Preheat the oven to 425°F (220°C).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Rinse the chicken under cold water and pat it dry with paper towels.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Season the chicken, inside and out, with salt and black pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> In a small bowl, mix olive oil (or melted butter), paprika, garlic powder, onion powder, dried herbs, and the juice of half a lemon.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Rub the chicken with the herb mixture, ensuring it\'s well-coated.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Stuff the cavity of the chicken with the remaining lemon half, crushed garlic cloves, and fresh rosemary sprigs.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Tie the legs of the chicken together with kitchen twine.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Place the chicken on a rack in a roasting pan, breast side up.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Roast in the preheated oven for about 20 minutes.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Reduce the oven temperature to 375°F (190°C) and continue roasting for an additional 60-80 minutes or until the internal temperature reaches 165°F (74°C) and the skin is golden and crispy.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 11:</b> Baste the chicken with chicken broth or white wine every 20-30 minutes to keep it moist.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 12:</b> Let the chicken rest for 10-15 minutes before carving.]]></string>

    <string name="apple_salad_title">Orange Roast Chicken</string>
    <string name="apple_salad_time">1hr 15min</string>
    <string name="apple_salad_calories">258kcal</string>
    <string name="apple_salad_fats">18g</string>
    <string name="apple_salad_proteins">9g</string>
    <string name="apple_salad_ingredients">• 1 whole chicken (about 4-5 lbs), giblets removed\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 2 tablespoons olive oil\n• Zest of 2 oranges\n• Juice of 2 oranges\n• 4 cloves garlic, minced\n• 2 tablespoons honey\n• 1 tablespoon Dijon mustard\n• 1 teaspoon ground coriander\n• 1 teaspoon ground cumin\n• 1 teaspoon smoked paprika\n• 1 teaspoon dried thyme\n• 1 teaspoon dried rosemary\n• 1/2 cup chicken broth or white wine (for basting)</string>
    <string name="apple_salad_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Preheat the oven to 425°F (220°C).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Rinse the chicken under cold water and pat it dry with paper towels.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Season the chicken, inside and out, with salt and black pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> In a bowl, whisk together olive oil, orange zest, orange juice, minced garlic, honey, Dijon mustard, ground coriander, ground cumin, smoked paprika, dried thyme, and dried rosemary.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Rub the chicken with the orange mixture, ensuring it\'s well-coated.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Place the chicken on a rack in a roasting pan, breast side up.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Roast in the preheated oven for about 20 minutes.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Reduce the oven temperature to 375°F (190°C) and continue roasting for an additional 60-80 minutes or until the internal temperature reaches 165°F (74°C) and the skin is golden and crispy.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Baste the chicken with chicken broth or white wine every 20-30 minutes to keep it moist.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Let the chicken rest for 10-15 minutes before carving.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 11:</b> Carve the roast chicken and serve it with the pan juices, and consider garnishing with orange slices for a decorative touch. Enjoy!]]></string>

    <string name="strawberry_salad_title">Persian Chicken Skewers</string>
    <string name="strawberry_salad_time">25min</string>
    <string name="strawberry_salad_calories">249kcal</string>
    <string name="strawberry_salad_fats">20g</string>
    <string name="strawberry_salad_proteins">6</string>
    <string name="strawberry_salad_ingredients">• 1.5 lbs boneless, skinless chicken thighs, cut into bite-sized pieces\n• 1 large onion, grated\n• 1/4 cup plain yogurt\n• 2 tablespoons olive oil\n• Juice of 1 lemon\n• 3 cloves garlic, minced\n• 1 teaspoon ground saffron (dissolved in 2 tablespoons hot water)\n• 1 teaspoon ground turmeric\n• 1 teaspoon ground cumin\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• Wooden or metal skewers</string>
    <string name="strawberry_salad_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> In a bowl, combine grated onion, yogurt, olive oil, lemon juice, minced garlic, dissolved saffron, ground turmeric, ground cumin, salt, and black pepper. Mix well to create the marinade.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Add the bite-sized chicken pieces to the marinade, ensuring they are well-coated. Cover the bowl and refrigerate for at least 2 hours, or preferably overnight.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> If using wooden skewers, soak them in water for about 30 minutes to prevent burning during grilling.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Preheat the grill or grill pan to medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Thread the marinated chicken pieces onto the skewers.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Grill the chicken skewers for about 8-10 minutes, turning occasionally, or until the chicken is fully cooked and has a nice char.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Optionally, baste the skewers with any remaining marinade or additional saffron water while grilling for extra flavor.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Serve the Persian Chicken Skewers with rice, lavash bread, or salad.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b>  Garnish with fresh herbs, lemon wedges, and serve with a side of rice or flatbread.]]></string>


    <!--    ##########  Low Carb Recipes-->

    <string name="scalloped_potatoes_title">Chicken Piccata</string>
    <string name="scalloped_potatoes_time">35min</string>
    <string name="scalloped_potatoes_calories">286kcal</string>
    <string name="scalloped_potatoes_fats">11g</string>
    <string name="scalloped_potatoes_proteins">9g</string>
    <string name="scalloped_potatoes_ingredients">• 4 boneless, skinless chicken breasts\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1 cup all-purpose flour, for dredging\n• 4 tablespoons unsalted butter\n• 4 tablespoons olive oil\n• 1/2 cup fresh lemon juice (about 2 lemons)\n• 1/2 cup chicken broth\n• 1/4 cup capers, drained\n• 1/4 cup chopped fresh parsley\n• Lemon slices for garnish</string>
    <string name="scalloped_potatoes_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b>Season the chicken breasts with salt and pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Dredge each chicken breast in flour, shaking off excess.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> In a large skillet, heat 2 tablespoons of butter and 2 tablespoons of olive oil over medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Add the chicken breasts and cook for about 3-4 minutes on each side or until they are golden brown and cooked through. Remove the chicken from the skillet and set aside.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> In the same skillet, add the remaining butter and olive oil.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Stir in lemon juice, chicken broth, and capers. Bring to a simmer.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Return the chicken to the skillet and simmer for an additional 5 minutes.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Transfer the chicken to a serving plate, pour the sauce over the top, and garnish with chopped parsley and lemon slices.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Chicken Piccata is often served with pasta, rice, or a side of vegetables.]]></string>

    <string name="classic_chicken_salad_title">Chicken Marsala</string>
    <string name="classic_chicken_salad_time">20min</string>
    <string name="classic_chicken_salad_calories">206kcal</string>
    <string name="classic_chicken_salad_fats">16g</string>
    <string name="classic_chicken_salad_proteins">13g</string>
    <string name="classic_chicken_salad_ingredients">• 4 boneless, skinless chicken breasts\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1 cup all-purpose flour, for dredging\n• 4 tablespoons olive oil\n• 8 oz cremini or button mushrooms, sliced\n• 3/4 cup Marsala wine\n• 3/4 cup chicken broth\n• 2 tablespoons unsalted butter\n• 2 tablespoons chopped fresh parsley</string>
    <string name="classic_chicken_salad_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Season the chicken breasts with salt and pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Dredge each chicken breast in flour, shaking off excess.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> In a large skillet, heat olive oil over medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Add the chicken breasts and cook for about 4-5 minutes on each side or until golden brown and cooked through. Remove the chicken from the skillet and set aside.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> In the same skillet, add the sliced mushrooms and cook until they release their moisture and become golden brown.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Pour in Marsala wine, scraping the bottom of the skillet to deglaze it.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Add chicken broth and bring the mixture to a simmer. Let it cook for about 5-7 minutes, allowing the sauce to reduce.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Stir in butter until melted and well incorporated.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Return the chicken to the skillet, coating it with the Marsala sauce. Cook for an additional 2-3 minutes.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Garnish with chopped parsley before serving.<br/><br/>

        <b>Step 11:</b> Chicken Marsala is often served with pasta, rice, or mashed potatoes.]]></string>

    <string name="jalapeno_chicken_salad_title">Chicken Francese</string>
    <string name="jalapeno_chicken_salad_time">35min</string>
    <string name="jalapeno_chicken_salad_calories">570kcal</string>
    <string name="jalapeno_chicken_salad_fats">13g</string>
    <string name="jalapeno_chicken_salad_proteins">18g</string>
    <string name="jalapeno_chicken_salad_ingredients">• 4 boneless, skinless chicken breasts\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1 cup all-purpose flour, for dredging\n• 4 large eggs\n• 1/4 cup grated Parmesan cheese\n• 4 tablespoons unsalted butter\n• 4 tablespoons olive oil\n• 1/2 cup dry white wine\n• 1 cup chicken broth\n• Juice of 1 lemon\n• 2 tablespoons chopped fresh parsley</string>
    <string name="jalapeno_chicken_salad_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Season the chicken breasts with salt and pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Dredge each chicken breast in flour, shaking off excess.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> In a bowl, whisk together eggs and Parmesan cheese.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Dip each chicken breast into the egg mixture, coating it well.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> In a large skillet, heat butter and olive oil over medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Add the chicken breasts and cook for about 3-4 minutes on each side or until golden brown and cooked through. Remove the chicken from the skillet and set aside.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Pour white wine into the skillet, scraping the bottom to deglaze it.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Add chicken broth and lemon juice. Bring the mixture to a simmer.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Return the chicken to the skillet and cook for an additional 2-3 minutes, allowing the sauce to thicken.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Garnish with chopped parsley before serving.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 11:</b>  Chicken Francese is often served with pasta, rice, or a side of vegetables.]]></string>

    <string name="crock_pot_whole_chicken_title">Chicken Cacciatore</string>
    <string name="crock_pot_whole_chicken_time">1hr 30min</string>
    <string name="crock_pot_whole_chicken_calories">335kcal</string>
    <string name="crock_pot_whole_chicken_fats">21g</string>
    <string name="crock_pot_whole_chicken_proteins">27g</string>
    <string name="crock_pot_whole_chicken_ingredients">• 4 bone-in, skin-on chicken thighs\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1 cup all-purpose flour, for dredging\n• 4 tablespoons olive oil\n• 1 onion, finely chopped\n• 1 bell pepper, sliced\n• 3 cloves garlic, minced\n• 1 cup mushrooms, sliced\n• 1 can (14 oz) crushed tomatoes\n• 1/2 cup dry red wine\n• 1/2 cup chicken broth\n• 1 teaspoon dried oregano\n• 1 teaspoon dried basil\n• 1/2 teaspoon dried thyme\n• 1/2 teaspoon red pepper flakes (optional)\n• 1 bay leaf\n• Fresh parsley for garnish</string>
    <string name="crock_pot_whole_chicken_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Season the chicken thighs with salt and pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Dredge each chicken thigh in flour, shaking off excess.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> In a large skillet, heat olive oil over medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Add the chicken thighs and cook for about 4-5 minutes on each side or until golden brown. Remove the chicken from the skillet and set aside.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> In the same skillet, add chopped onion, sliced bell pepper, and minced garlic. Sauté until the vegetables are softened.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Add sliced mushrooms and cook until they release their moisture.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Pour in red wine, scraping the bottom of the skillet to deglaze it.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Stir in crushed tomatoes, chicken broth, dried oregano, dried basil, dried thyme, red pepper flakes (if using), and add the bay leaf.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Return the chicken thighs to the skillet and let it simmer for about 25-30 minutes or until the chicken is cooked through and the sauce has thickened.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Garnish with fresh parsley before serving.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 11:</b> Chicken Cacciatore is often served with pasta, rice, or crusty bread.]]></string>

    <string name="crock_pot_cheesy_chicken_title">Chicken Parmesan</string>
    <string name="crock_pot_cheesy_chicken_time">38min</string>
    <string name="crock_pot_cheesy_chicken_calories">594kcal</string>
    <string name="crock_pot_cheesy_chicken_fats">23g</string>
    <string name="crock_pot_cheesy_chicken_proteins">43g</string>
    <string name="crock_pot_cheesy_chicken_ingredients">• 4 boneless, skinless chicken breasts\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1 cup all-purpose flour, for dredging\n• 2 large eggs\n• 2 cups Italian-style breadcrumbs\n• 1 cup grated Parmesan cheese\n• 1 cup mozzarella cheese, shredded\n• Olive oil for frying\n• 2 tablespoons olive oil\n• 1 onion, finely chopped\n• 2 cloves garlic, minced\n• 1 can (28 oz) crushed tomatoes\n• 1 teaspoon dried oregano\n• 1 teaspoon dried basil\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1/2 teaspoon sugar (optional, to balance acidity)\n• Fresh basil or parsley for garnish\n• Cooked spaghetti or your favorite pasta</string>
    <string name="crock_pot_cheesy_chicken_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> In a saucepan, heat olive oil over medium heat. Add chopped onion and sauté until softened.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Add minced garlic and cook until fragrant.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Pour in crushed tomatoes and add dried oregano, dried basil, salt, and pepper. If the sauce is too acidic, add sugar to balance the flavors.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Simmer the sauce on low heat for about 20-30 minutes, stirring occasionally.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Preheat the oven to 375°F (190°C).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Season chicken breasts with salt and pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Dredge each chicken breast in flour, dip in beaten eggs, and coat with a mixture of breadcrumbs and grated Parmesan.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> In a large skillet, heat olive oil over medium-high heat. Fry the chicken breasts until golden brown on both sides. Transfer to a paper towel to drain excess oil.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> In a baking dish, spread a thin layer of tomato sauce.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Place the fried chicken breasts on top of the sauce.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 11:</b> Spoon more tomato sauce over each chicken breast.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 12:</b> Sprinkle shredded mozzarella and grated Parmesan over the chicken.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 13:</b> Bake in the preheated oven for about 20-25 minutes or until the cheese is melted and bubbly.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 14:</b> Optionally, broil for a couple of minutes until the cheese is golden brown.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 15:</b> Garnish with fresh basil or parsley before serving.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 16:</b> Chicken Parmesan is often served over cooked spaghetti or your favorite pasta.]]></string>

    <string name="tandoori_salmon_title">Italian Baked Chicken</string>
    <string name="tandoori_salmon_time">25min</string>
    <string name="tandoori_salmon_calories">280kcal</string>
    <string name="tandoori_salmon_fats">14g</string>
    <string name="tandoori_salmon_proteins">30g</string>
    <string name="tandoori_salmon_ingredients">• 4 boneless, skinless chicken breasts\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 2 tablespoons olive oil\n• 4 cloves garlic, minced\n• 1 can (14 oz) diced tomatoes, drained\n• 1 teaspoon dried oregano\n• 1 teaspoon dried basil\n• 1/2 teaspoon dried thyme\n• 1/2 teaspoon dried rosemary\n• 1/2 cup grated Parmesan cheese\n• Fresh basil or parsley for garnish</string>
    <string name="tandoori_salmon_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Preheat the oven to 375°F (190°C).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Season chicken breasts with salt and black pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> In a large oven-safe skillet, heat olive oil over medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Add minced garlic and sauté until fragrant.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Place chicken breasts in the skillet and sear on each side until golden brown.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Add diced tomatoes, dried oregano, dried basil, dried thyme, and dried rosemary to the skillet, distributing them evenly around the chicken.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Sprinkle grated Parmesan cheese over the chicken and tomatoes.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Transfer the skillet to the preheated oven and bake for about 20-25 minutes or until the chicken is cooked through.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Garnish with fresh basil or parsley before serving.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Italian Baked Chicken can be served with a side of pasta, rice, or a green salad.]]></string>

    <string name="cashew_chicken_curry_title">Chicken Alfredo</string>
    <string name="cashew_chicken_curry_time">40min</string>
    <string name="cashew_chicken_curry_calories">287kcal</string>
    <string name="cashew_chicken_curry_fats">19g</string>
    <string name="cashew_chicken_curry_proteins">22g</string>
    <string name="cashew_chicken_curry_ingredients">• 8 oz fettuccine pasta\n• 2 boneless, skinless chicken breasts, thinly sliced\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 2 tablespoons olive oil\n• 4 cloves garlic, minced\n• 1 cup heavy cream\n• 1 cup grated Parmesan cheese\n• 1/2 cup unsalted butter\n• 1 teaspoon garlic powder\n• 1/2 teaspoon nutmeg (optional)\n• Fresh parsley for garnish</string>
    <string name="cashew_chicken_curry_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Cook fettuccine pasta according to package instructions. Drain and set aside.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Season sliced chicken breasts with salt and black pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> In a large skillet, heat olive oil over medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Add sliced chicken to the skillet and cook until golden brown and cooked through. Remove the chicken from the skillet and set aside.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> In the same skillet, add minced garlic and sauté until fragrant.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Reduce heat to medium-low, add butter to the skillet, and let it melt.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Pour in heavy cream, stirring continuously.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Gradually add grated Parmesan cheese, stirring until the sauce is smooth and well combined.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Stir in garlic powder and nutmeg (if using). Adjust salt and pepper to taste.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Add the cooked fettuccine pasta and sliced chicken to the skillet. Toss to coat the pasta and chicken evenly with the Alfredo sauce.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 11:</b> Garnish with fresh parsley before serving.<br/><br/>

        <b>Step 12:</b> Chicken Alfredo is often served hot, garnished with additional Parmesan cheese and a sprinkle of black pepper.]]></string>

    <string name="winnipeg_chicken_curry_title">Chicken Pizzaiola</string>
    <string name="winnipeg_chicken_curry_time">50min</string>
    <string name="winnipeg_chicken_curry_calories">328kcal</string>
    <string name="winnipeg_chicken_curry_fats">21g</string>
    <string name="winnipeg_chicken_curry_proteins">19g</string>
    <string name="winnipeg_chicken_curry_ingredients">• 4 boneless, skinless chicken breasts\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1/2 cup all-purpose flour, for dredging\n• 2 tablespoons olive oil\n• 1 onion, thinly sliced\n• 2 cloves garlic, minced\n• 1 can (14 oz) crushed tomatoes\n• 1 teaspoon dried oregano\n• 1 teaspoon dried basil\n• 1/2 teaspoon red pepper flakes (optional)\n• 1/2 cup shredded mozzarella cheese\n• Fresh basil or parsley for garnish</string>
    <string name="winnipeg_chicken_curry_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Season chicken breasts with salt and black pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Dredge each chicken breast in flour, shaking off excess.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> In a large skillet, heat olive oil over medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Add chicken breasts and cook for about 3-4 minutes on each side or until golden brown. Remove the chicken from the skillet and set aside.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> In the same skillet, add sliced onions and sauté until softened.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Add minced garlic and cook until fragrant.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Pour in crushed tomatoes and add dried oregano, dried basil, and red pepper flakes (if using). Stir to combine.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Return the chicken to the skillet, spooning some of the tomato mixture over each piece.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Sprinkle shredded mozzarella cheese over each chicken breast.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Cover the skillet and let it simmer for an additional 10-15 minutes or until the chicken is cooked through, and the cheese is melted and bubbly.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 11:</b> Garnish with fresh basil or parsley before serving.<br/><br/>

        <b>Step 9:</b> Chicken Pizzaiola is often served over pasta, rice, or with a side of crusty bread.]]></string>

    <string name="chili_chicken_title">Chicken Arrabbiata</string>
    <string name="chili_chicken_time">45</string>
    <string name="chili_chicken_calories">444kcal</string>
    <string name="chili_chicken_fats">26g</string>
    <string name="chili_chicken_proteins">23g</string>
    <string name="chili_chicken_ingredients">• 4 boneless, skinless chicken breasts\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 2 tablespoons olive oil\n• 4 cloves garlic, minced\n• 1/2 teaspoon red pepper flakes (adjust to taste)\n• 1 can (14 oz) crushed tomatoes\n• 1 teaspoon dried oregano\n• 1 teaspoon dried basil\n• 1/2 cup black olives, sliced (optional)\n• Fresh basil or parsley for garnish\n• Grated Parmesan cheese for serving</string>
    <string name="chili_chicken_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Season chicken breasts with salt and black pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> In a large skillet, heat olive oil over medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Add chicken breasts and cook for about 4-5 minutes on each side or until golden brown and cooked through. Remove the chicken from the skillet and set aside.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> In the same skillet, add minced garlic and red pepper flakes. Sauté for about 1-2 minutes until the garlic is fragrant.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Pour in crushed tomatoes and add dried oregano and dried basil. Stir to combine.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> If using black olives, add them to the sauce and mix well.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Return the cooked chicken to the skillet, spooning some of the sauce over each piece.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Simmer the chicken in the sauce for an additional 5-7 minutes to allow the flavors to meld.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Garnish with fresh basil or parsley before serving.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Chicken Arrabbiata is often served over pasta, rice, or with crusty bread. Sprinkle with grated Parmesan cheese for added flavor.]]></string>

    <string name="italian_salad_dressing_title">Italian Peasant Soup</string>
    <string name="italian_salad_dressing_time">40min</string>
    <string name="italian_salad_dressing_calories">148kcal</string>
    <string name="italian_salad_dressing_fats">16g</string>
    <string name="italian_salad_dressing_proteins">3g</string>
    <string name="italian_salad_dressing_ingredients">• 2 tablespoons olive oil\n• 1 onion, finely chopped\n• 2 carrots, diced\n• 2 celery stalks, diced\n• 3 cloves garlic, minced\n• 1 can (14 oz) diced tomatoes\n• 1 can (15 oz) cannellini beans, drained and rinsed\n• 1 zucchini, diced\n• 1 cup green beans, chopped\n• 1 cup cabbage, shredded\n• 1 cup kale or spinach, chopped\n• 8 cups chicken or vegetable broth\n• 1 teaspoon dried thyme\n• 1 teaspoon dried rosemary\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1 cup small pasta (like ditalini or small shells)\n• Grated Parmesan cheese for serving\n•Fresh parsley for garnish</string>
    <string name="italian_salad_dressing_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> In a large pot, heat olive oil over medium heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Add chopped onion, diced carrots, and diced celery. Sauté until the vegetables are softened.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Add minced garlic and cook until fragrant.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Pour in diced tomatoes and cannellini beans. Stir to combine.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Add diced zucchini, chopped green beans, shredded cabbage, and chopped kale or spinach to the pot.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Pour in chicken or vegetable broth and add dried thyme and dried rosemary. Season with salt and black pepper to taste.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Bring the soup to a simmer and let it cook for about 15-20 minutes, allowing the vegetables to become tender.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Add small pasta to the soup and cook according to the package instructions until the pasta is al dente.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Adjust seasoning if needed and remove the soup from heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Serve the Italian Peasant Soup hot, garnished with grated Parmesan cheese and fresh parsley.]]></string>

    <string name="award_winning_chili_title">Tuscan Chicken Stew</string>
    <string name="award_winning_chili_time">50min</string>
    <string name="award_winning_chili_calories">301kcal</string>
    <string name="award_winning_chili_fats">64f</string>
    <string name="award_winning_chili_proteins">24g</string>
    <string name="award_winning_chili_ingredients">• 1.5 lbs boneless, skinless chicken thighs, cut into bite-sized pieces\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 2 tablespoons olive oil\n• 1 onion, finely chopped\n• 3 cloves garlic, minced\n• 1 carrot, diced\n• 1 celery stalk, diced\n• 1 red bell pepper, diced\n• 1 can (14 oz) diced tomatoes\n• 1 can (15 oz) cannellini beans, drained and rinsed\n• 1/2 cup sun-dried tomatoes, chopped\n• 4 cups chicken broth\n• 1 teaspoon dried rosemary\n• 1 teaspoon dried thyme\n• 1/2 teaspoon red pepper flakes (optional)\n• 1 cup baby spinach\n• 1/4 cup fresh basil, chopped\n•Grated Parmesan cheese for serving</string>
    <string name="award_winning_chili_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Season chicken thighs with salt and black pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> In a large pot, heat olive oil over medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Add the chicken pieces and brown them on all sides. Once browned, remove the chicken from the pot and set aside.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> In the same pot, add chopped onion, minced garlic, diced carrot, diced celery, and diced red bell pepper. Sauté until the vegetables are softened.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Pour in diced tomatoes, cannellini beans, and sun-dried tomatoes. Stir to combine.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Return the browned chicken to the pot.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Add chicken broth, dried rosemary, dried thyme, and red pepper flakes (if using). Bring the stew to a simmer.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Let the stew cook for about 20-25 minutes, allowing the flavors to meld and the chicken to cook through.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Stir in baby spinach and chopped fresh basil. Cook for an additional 2-3 minutes until the spinach wilts.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Adjust seasoning if needed.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 11:</b> Serve the Tuscan Chicken Stew hot, garnished with grated Parmesan cheese.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 12:</b>  Tuscan Chicken Stew is often served with crusty bread or over cooked pasta.]]></string>

    <string name="bourbon_chicken_title">Chicken Gnocchi Soup</string>
    <string name="bourbon_chicken_time">45min</string>
    <string name="bourbon_chicken_calories">522kcal</string>
    <string name="bourbon_chicken_fats">24g</string>
    <string name="bourbon_chicken_proteins">50g</string>
    <string name="bourbon_chicken_ingredients">• 2 tablespoons butter\n• 1 onion, finely chopped\n• 2 carrots, diced\n• 2 celery stalks, diced\n• 3 cloves garlic, minced\n• 1 lb boneless, skinless chicken breasts, cooked and shredded\n• 4 cups chicken broth\n• 1 teaspoon dried thyme\n• 1 teaspoon dried rosemary\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1 package (16 oz) potato gnocchi\n• 2 cups fresh spinach or kale, chopped\n• 1 cup half-and-half or heavy cream\n• Grated Parmesan cheese for serving\n• Fresh parsley for garnish</string>
    <string name="bourbon_chicken_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> In a large pot, melt butter over medium heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Add chopped onion, diced carrots, diced celery, and minced garlic. Sauté until the vegetables are softened.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Add shredded chicken to the pot and stir to combine.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Pour in chicken broth and add dried thyme, dried rosemary, salt, and black pepper. Bring the soup to a simmer.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Add potato gnocchi to the simmering soup. Cook according to the package instructions until the gnocchi float to the surface.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Stir in chopped spinach or kale and let it wilt.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Pour in half-and-half or heavy cream, stirring to combine. Simmer for an additional 5-7 minutes.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Adjust seasoning if needed.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Serve the Chicken Gnocchi Soup hot, garnished with grated Parmesan cheese and fresh parsley.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Chicken Gnocchi Soup is often served with crusty bread or a side salad.]]></string>


    <!--    ##########  Healthy Dinner Recipes-->

    <string name="roasted_potato_salad_title">Mexican Chicken Fajitas</string>
    <string name="roasted_potato_salad_time">45min</string>
    <string name="roasted_potato_salad_calories">313kcal</string>
    <string name="roasted_potato_salad_fats">12g</string>
    <string name="roasted_potato_salad_proteins">5g</string>
    <string name="roasted_potato_salad_ingredients">• 1 lb boneless, skinless chicken breasts, sliced into strips\n• 1 bell pepper (any color), sliced\n• 1 onion, sliced\n• 2 tablespoons olive oil\n• 2 teaspoons chili powder\n• 1 teaspoon cumin\n• 1 teaspoon paprika\n• 1/2 teaspoon garlic powder\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• Flour or corn tortillas\n• Optional toppings: salsa, guacamole, sour cream, shredded cheese, cilantro</string>
    <string name="roasted_potato_salad_instruction"><![CDATA[
         <b>Step 1:</b> In a bowl, mix together chili powder, cumin, paprika, garlic powder, salt, and black pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Season chicken strips with half of the spice mixture.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> In a large skillet, heat olive oil over medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Add sliced bell pepper and onion to the skillet. Sauté until vegetables are slightly tender.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Push the vegetables to one side of the skillet and add the seasoned chicken strips to the other side.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Cook chicken until browned and cooked through.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Combine the chicken with the vegetables and sprinkle the remaining spice mixture over everything. Toss to coat evenly.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Warm the tortillas in the skillet or in the oven.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Serve the chicken and vegetable mixture in the tortillas.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Top with your choice of salsa, guacamole, sour cream, shredded cheese, and cilantro.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 11:</b> Chicken Fajitas are often served with rice, beans, or a side of Mexican-style corn.]]></string>

    <string name="crock_pot_rice_pudding_title">Mexican Chicken Chilli</string>
    <string name="crock_pot_rice_pudding_time">1hr</string>
    <string name="crock_pot_rice_pudding_calories">316kcal</string>
    <string name="crock_pot_rice_pudding_fats">10g</string>
    <string name="crock_pot_rice_pudding_proteins">7g</string>
    <string name="crock_pot_rice_pudding_ingredients">• 1 lb ground chicken\n• 1 onion, finely chopped\n• 3 cloves garlic, minced\n• 1 bell pepper (any color), diced\n• 1 can (14 oz) diced tomatoes\n• 1 can (15 oz) black beans, drained and rinsed\n• 1 cup frozen corn\n• 1 can (4 oz) diced green chilies\n• 2 tablespoons chili powder\n• 1 teaspoon ground cumin\n• 1 teaspoon smoked paprika\n• 1/2 teaspoon dried oregano\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 3 cups chicken broth\n• 1 lime, juiced\n• Fresh cilantro for garnish\n• Shredded cheese, sour cream, avocado for topping (optional)</string>
    <string name="crock_pot_rice_pudding_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> In a large pot, brown ground chicken over medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Add chopped onion, minced garlic, and diced bell pepper. Sauté until vegetables are softened.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Stir in chili powder, ground cumin, smoked paprika, dried oregano, salt, and black pepper. Cook for 1-2 minutes until fragrant.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Pour in diced tomatoes, black beans, kidney beans, frozen corn, and diced green chilies. Mix well.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Add chicken broth to the pot. Bring the mixture to a simmer.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Reduce heat to low, cover the pot, and let it simmer for about 15-20 minutes, allowing the flavors to meld.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Just before serving, stir in lime juice.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Adjust seasoning if needed.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Serve the Mexican Chicken Chili hot, garnished with fresh cilantro and your choice of toppings like shredded cheese, sour cream, or sliced avocado.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Mexican Chicken Chili is often served with crusty bread, tortilla chips, or over rice.]]></string>

    <string name="tandoori_chicken_title">Mexican Grilled Chicken</string>
    <string name="tandoori_chicken_time">25min</string>
    <string name="tandoori_chicken_calories">182kcal</string>
    <string name="tandoori_chicken_fats">12g</string>
    <string name="tandoori_chicken_proteins">13g</string>
    <string name="tandoori_chicken_ingredients">• 4 boneless, skinless chicken breasts\n• 2 tablespoons olive oil\n• 2 cloves garlic, minced\n• 1 teaspoon ground cumin\n• 1 teaspoon chili powder\n• 1 teaspoon paprika\n• 1/2 teaspoon dried oregano\n• 1/2 teaspoon onion powder\n• 1/2 teaspoon garlic powder\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• Juice of 2 limes\n• Fresh cilantro for garnish\n• Lime wedges for serving</string>
    <string name="tandoori_chicken_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> In a bowl, mix together olive oil, minced garlic, ground cumin, chili powder, paprika, dried oregano, onion powder, garlic powder, salt, and black pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Place the chicken breasts in a resealable plastic bag or shallow dish and pour the marinade over them. Massage the marinade into the chicken, ensuring it\'s well coated. Marinate in the refrigerator for at least 30 minutes or up to 4 hours.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Preheat the grill to medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Remove the chicken from the refrigerator and let it come to room temperature for about 15 minutes.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Grill the chicken breasts for approximately 6-8 minutes per side or until they reach an internal temperature of 165°F (74°C) and have nice grill marks.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> During the last few minutes of grilling, baste the chicken with lime juice.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Remove the chicken from the grill and let it rest for a few minutes.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Garnish with fresh cilantro and serve with lime wedges.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Mexican Grilled Chicken is versatile and can be served with rice, beans, in tacos, on salads, or alongside your favorite Mexican sides.]]></string>

    <string name="black_bean_couscous_salad_title">Mexican Chicken Casserole</string>
    <string name="black_bean_couscous_salad_time">75min</string>
    <string name="black_bean_couscous_salad_calories">253kcal</string>
    <string name="black_bean_couscous_salad_fats">6g</string>
    <string name="black_bean_couscous_salad_proteins">10g</string>
    <string name="black_bean_couscous_salad_ingredients">• 2 cups cooked and shredded chicken\n• 1 can (15 oz) black beans, drained and rinsed\n• 1 cup corn kernels (fresh, frozen, or canned)\n• 1 cup diced bell peppers (any color)\n• 1 cup diced tomatoes\n• 1 cup shredded Mexican blend cheese\n• 1/2 cup chopped green onions\n• 1/2 cup chopped fresh cilantro\n• 1 teaspoon ground cumin\n• 1 teaspoon chili powder\n• 1/2 teaspoon garlic powder\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1 can (10 oz) enchilada sauce\n• 1 cup sour cream\n• 2 cups crushed tortilla chips\n• Lime wedges for serving</string>
    <string name="black_bean_couscous_salad_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Preheat the oven to 375°F (190°C).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> In a large bowl, combine shredded chicken, black beans, corn, bell peppers, diced tomatoes, shredded cheese, green onions, cilantro, ground cumin, chili powder, garlic powder, salt, and black pepper. Mix well.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> In a separate bowl, whisk together enchilada sauce and sour cream.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Add half of the enchilada sauce mixture to the chicken mixture and toss until well combined.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Grease a baking dish and spread half of the crushed tortilla chips on the bottom.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Spoon the chicken mixture over the chips, spreading it evenly.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Pour the remaining enchilada sauce mixture over the chicken mixture.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Top with the remaining crushed tortilla chips.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Bake in the preheated oven for 25-30 minutes or until the casserole is hot and bubbly.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Remove from the oven and let it cool for a few minutes.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 11:</b> Garnish with additional green onions and cilantro.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 12:</b> Serve the Mexican Chicken Casserole warm with lime wedges on the side.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 13:</b> Mexican Chicken Casserole is often served with a side of rice, a green salad, or additional toppings like sliced avocado.]]></string>

    <string name="chicken_noodle_soup_title">Mexican Chicken Spaghetti</string>
    <string name="chicken_noodle_soup_time">2hr</string>
    <string name="chicken_noodle_soup_calories">247kcal</string>
    <string name="chicken_noodle_soup_fats">9g</string>
    <string name="chicken_noodle_soup_proteins">21g</string>
    <string name="chicken_noodle_soup_ingredients">• 8 oz spaghetti\n• 2 cups cooked and shredded chicken\n• 1 can (10 oz) diced tomatoes with green chilies (like Rotel)\n• 1/2 cup diced onion\n• 1/2 cup diced bell peppers (any color)\n• 2 cloves garlic, minced\n• 1 teaspoon ground cumin\n• 1 teaspoon chili powder\n• 1/2 teaspoon dried oregano\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1 can (10.5 oz) cream of chicken soup\n• 1/2 cup chicken broth\n• 1 cup shredded Mexican blend cheese\n• 1/4 cup chopped fresh cilantro\n• Lime wedges for serving</string>
    <string name="chicken_noodle_soup_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Cook the spaghetti according to the package instructions. Drain and set aside.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> In a large skillet, sauté diced onion, bell peppers, and minced garlic until softened.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Add shredded chicken, diced tomatoes with green chilies, ground cumin, chili powder, dried oregano, salt, and black pepper to the skillet. Stir to combine.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> In a separate bowl, whisk together cream of chicken soup and chicken broth.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Pour the soup mixture over the chicken mixture in the skillet. Mix well.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Add the cooked spaghetti to the skillet and toss until everything is well coated.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Transfer the mixture to a greased baking dish.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Sprinkle shredded cheese over the top.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Bake in a preheated oven at 350°F (175°C) for 20-25 minutes or until the cheese is melted and bubbly.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Remove from the oven and garnish with chopped cilantro.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 11:</b> Serve the Mexican Chicken Spaghetti warm with lime wedges on the side.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 12:</b> Mexican Chicken Spaghetti can be served with a side of garlic bread or a simple green salad.]]></string>

    <string name="chicken_tortilla_soup_title">Mexican Chicken Soup</string>
    <string name="chicken_tortilla_soup_time">260min</string>
    <string name="chicken_tortilla_soup_calories">352kcal</string>
    <string name="chicken_tortilla_soup_fats">18g</string>
    <string name="chicken_tortilla_soup_proteins">20g</string>
    <string name="chicken_tortilla_soup_ingredients">• 1 lb boneless, skinless chicken thighs or breasts\n• 1 tablespoon olive oil\n• 1 onion, finely chopped\n• 3 cloves garlic, minced\n• 1 jalapeño, seeded and minced\n• 2 carrots, sliced\n• 2 celery stalks, sliced\n• 1 can (14 oz) diced tomatoes\n• 1 can (15 oz) black beans, drained and rinsed\n• 1 cup corn kernels (fresh, frozen, or canned)\n• 1 teaspoon ground cumin\n• 1 teaspoon chili powder\n• 1/2 teaspoon dried oregano\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 6 cups chicken broth\n• Juice of 2 limes\n• Fresh cilantro for garnish\n• Avocado slices for serving\n• Tortilla strips or crushed tortilla chips for topping</string>
    <string name="chicken_tortilla_soup_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> In a large pot, heat olive oil over medium heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Add chopped onion, minced garlic, and jalapeño. Sauté until the vegetables are softened.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Add chicken thighs or breasts to the pot and brown on both sides.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Stir in sliced carrots and celery.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Pour in diced tomatoes, black beans, and corn. Add ground cumin, chili powder, dried oregano, salt, and black pepper. Mix well.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Pour in chicken broth and bring the soup to a simmer.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Cover the pot and let it simmer for about 20-25 minutes, or until the chicken is cooked through.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Remove the chicken from the pot and shred it using two forks.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Return the shredded chicken to the pot and stir in lime juice.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Adjust seasoning if needed.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 11:</b> Serve the Mexican Chicken Soup hot, garnished with fresh cilantro, avocado slices, and tortilla strips.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 12:</b> Mexican Chicken Soup is often served with lime wedges on the side and can be accompanied by warm tortillas.]]></string>

    <string name="creamy_garlic_penne_pasta_title">Mexican Fried Chicken</string>
    <string name="creamy_garlic_penne_pasta_time">1hr</string>
    <string name="creamy_garlic_penne_pasta_calories">368kcal</string>
    <string name="creamy_garlic_penne_pasta_fats">8g</string>
    <string name="creamy_garlic_penne_pasta_proteins">9g</string>
    <string name="creamy_garlic_penne_pasta_ingredients">• 2 lbs chicken pieces (drumsticks, thighs, wings)\n• Juice of 2 limes\n• 2 cloves garlic, minced\n• 1 teaspoon ground cumin\n• 1 teaspoon chili powder\n• 1/2 teaspoon paprika\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1 cup all-purpose flour\n• 1 teaspoon ground cumin\n• 1 teaspoon chili powder\n• 1/2 teaspoon paprika\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• Vegetable oil for frying</string>
    <string name="creamy_garlic_penne_pasta_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> In a bowl, combine lime juice, minced garlic, ground cumin, chili powder, paprika, salt, and black pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Place the chicken pieces in a resealable plastic bag or bowl, pour the marinade over them, and ensure each piece is well-coated.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Marinate in the refrigerator for at least 2 hours, preferably overnight.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> In a shallow dish, mix flour, ground cumin, chili powder, paprika, salt, and black pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Take each marinated chicken piece, allowing excess marinade to drip off, and coat it evenly with the flour mixture. Press the coating onto the chicken for better adherence.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> In a large skillet or deep fryer, heat vegetable oil to 350°F (180°C).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Carefully place the coated chicken pieces into the hot oil, a few at a time, without overcrowding.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Fry until the chicken is golden brown and crispy, turning occasionally to ensure even cooking. This usually takes about 12-15 minutes, depending on the size of the pieces.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b>  Once the chicken is cooked through and crispy, use a slotted spoon to transfer it to a paper towel-lined plate to drain excess oil.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Serve the Mexican fried chicken hot, garnished with lime wedges and accompanied by your favorite dipping sauce.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 11:</b> Mexican Fried Chicken is often served with sides like Mexican rice, coleslaw, or a fresh salad. Enjoy it as a flavorful and crispy main dish.]]></string>

    <string name="baked_parmesan_fish_title">Crockpot Mexican Chicken</string>
    <string name="baked_parmesan_fish_time">220min</string>
    <string name="baked_parmesan_fish_calories">198kcal</string>
    <string name="baked_parmesan_fish_fats">5g</string>
    <string name="baked_parmesan_fish_proteins">31g</string>
    <string name="baked_parmesan_fish_ingredients">• 2 lbs boneless, skinless chicken breasts\n• 1 can (15 oz) black beans, drained and rinsed\n• 1 can (15 oz) corn kernels, drained\n• 1 can (14 oz) diced tomatoes with green chilies (like Rotel)\n• 1 onion, finely chopped\n• 1 bell pepper (any color), diced\n• 3 cloves garlic, minced\n• 1 teaspoon ground cumin\n• 1 teaspoon chili powder\n• 1 teaspoon paprika\n• 1/2 teaspoon dried oregano\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1 cup chicken broth\n• Juice of 2 limes\n• Fresh cilantro for garnish\n• Cooked rice or tortillas for serving</string>
    <string name="baked_parmesan_fish_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Place chicken breasts at the bottom of the crockpot.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Add black beans, corn, diced tomatoes with green chilies, chopped onion, diced bell pepper, minced garlic, ground cumin, chili powder, paprika, dried oregano, salt, and black pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Pour chicken broth over the ingredients in the crockpot.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Cover and cook on low heat for 6-8 hours or on high heat for 3-4 hours, or until the chicken is tender and easily shreddable.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Using two forks, shred the cooked chicken directly in the crockpot.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Squeeze lime juice over the shredded chicken mixture and stir to combine.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Taste and adjust the seasoning if needed.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Serve the Crockpot Mexican Chicken over cooked rice or in tortillas.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Garnish with fresh cilantro.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Crockpot Mexican Chicken can be served over rice, inside tortillas for tacos or burritos, or alongside your favorite Mexican sides.]]></string>

    <string name="greek_baked_fish_title">Chicken Burritos</string>
    <string name="greek_baked_fish_time">35min</string>
    <string name="greek_baked_fish_calories">160kcal</string>
    <string name="greek_baked_fish_fats">6g</string>
    <string name="greek_baked_fish_proteins">27g</string>
    <string name="greek_baked_fish_ingredients">• 1 lb boneless, skinless chicken breasts, cooked and shredded\n• 1 tablespoon olive oil\n• 1 onion, finely chopped\n• 2 cloves garlic, minced\n• 1 bell pepper, diced\n• 1 cup cooked black beans\n• 1 cup cooked rice\n• 1 cup corn kernels (fresh, frozen, or canned)\n• 1 teaspoon ground cumin\n• 1 teaspoon chili powder\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 4 large flour tortillas\n• 1 cup shredded Mexican blend cheese\n• Salsa, guacamole, sour cream, and fresh cilantro for garnish</string>
    <string name="greek_baked_fish_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> In a large skillet, heat olive oil over medium heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Add chopped onion and minced garlic. Sauté until the onion is translucent.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Add diced bell pepper and cook until softened.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Stir in shredded chicken, black beans, cooked rice, corn, ground cumin, and chili powder. Mix well to combine.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Season with salt and black pepper to taste. Cook for an additional 5-7 minutes to heat through.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Warm the flour tortillas in a dry skillet or microwave.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Spoon the chicken mixture onto each tortilla.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Sprinkle shredded cheese over the chicken mixture.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Fold the sides of the tortilla inwards and then roll it up tightly to form a burrito.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Optionally, heat the burritos in a skillet or oven to melt the cheese.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 11:</b> Garnish with salsa, guacamole, sour cream, and fresh cilantro.]]></string>

    <string name="dutch_cucumber_salad_title">Chicken Tacos</string>
    <string name="dutch_cucumber_salad_time">45min</string>
    <string name="dutch_cucumber_salad_calories">43kcal</string>
    <string name="dutch_cucumber_salad_fats">3g</string>
    <string name="dutch_cucumber_salad_proteins">2g</string>
    <string name="dutch_cucumber_salad_ingredients">• 1 lb boneless, skinless chicken thighs or breasts, cooked and shredded\n• 1 tablespoon olive oil\n• 1 onion, finely chopped\n• 2 cloves garlic, minced\n• 1 teaspoon ground cumin\n• 1 teaspoon chili powder\n• 1/2 teaspoon paprika\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1 cup diced tomatoes\n• 1 cup shredded lettuce\n• 1 cup shredded Mexican blend cheese\n• 1/2 cup chopped fresh cilantro\n• 1/4 cup diced red onion\n• 8 small flour or corn tortillas\n• Lime wedges for serving\n• Salsa, guacamole, and sour cream for topping</string>
    <string name="dutch_cucumber_salad_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> In a skillet, heat olive oil over medium heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Add chopped onion and minced garlic. Sauté until the onion is translucent.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Stir in shredded chicken, ground cumin, chili powder, paprika, salt, and black pepper. Cook for 5-7 minutes until the chicken is heated through and coated with spices.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Warm the tortillas in a dry skillet or microwave.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Assemble the tacos by placing a portion of the seasoned chicken onto each tortilla.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Top with diced tomatoes, shredded lettuce, Mexican blend cheese, chopped cilantro, and diced red onion.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Squeeze fresh lime juice over the tacos.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Serve the chicken tacos with salsa, guacamole, and sour cream on the side.<br/><br/>

        <b>Step 9:</b> Chicken Tacos are often served with a side of rice and beans or a simple Mexican slaw.]]></string>

    <string name="crispy_ginger_beef_title">Chicken Flautas</string>
    <string name="crispy_ginger_beef_time">50min</string>
    <string name="crispy_ginger_beef_calories">945kcal</string>
    <string name="crispy_ginger_beef_fats">31g</string>
    <string name="crispy_ginger_beef_proteins">58g</string>
    <string name="crispy_ginger_beef_ingredients">• 1 lb boneless, skinless chicken thighs or breasts, cooked and shredded\n• 1 tablespoon olive oil\n• 1 onion, finely chopped\n• 2 cloves garlic, minced\n• 1 teaspoon ground cumin\n• 1 teaspoon chili powder\n• 1/2 teaspoon paprika\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 8 small flour or corn tortillas\n• 1 cup shredded Mexican blend cheese\n• Vegetable oil for frying\n• Sour cream, guacamole, and salsa for serving\n• Shredded lettuce and diced tomatoes for garnish\n• Fresh cilantro for topping</string>
    <string name="crispy_ginger_beef_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> In a skillet, heat olive oil over medium heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Add chopped onion and minced garlic. Sauté until the onion is translucent.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Stir in shredded chicken, ground cumin, chili powder, paprika, salt, and black pepper. Cook for 5-7 minutes until the chicken is heated through and coated with spices.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Warm the tortillas in a dry skillet or microwave.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Place a portion of the seasoned chicken onto each tortilla, sprinkle with shredded cheese, and roll tightly to form a flute shape.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> In a separate skillet, heat vegetable oil for frying over medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Carefully place the rolled flautas seam-side down into the hot oil. Fry until golden brown and crispy on all sides.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Remove the flautas from the oil and place them on a paper towel to drain any excess oil.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Serve the Chicken Flautas hot, topped with shredded lettuce, diced tomatoes, fresh cilantro, sour cream, guacamole, and salsa.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b>  Chicken Flautas are often served with Mexican rice, refried beans, or a side salad.]]></string>

    <string name="crock_pot_stuffing_title">Chicken Lime Soup</string>
    <string name="crock_pot_stuffing_time">45min</string>
    <string name="crock_pot_stuffing_calories">254kcal</string>
    <string name="crock_pot_stuffing_fats">17g</string>
    <string name="crock_pot_stuffing_proteins">5g</string>
    <string name="crock_pot_stuffing_ingredients">• 1 lb boneless, skinless chicken breasts, cooked and shredded\n• 1 tablespoon olive oil\n• 1 onion, finely chopped\n• 3 cloves garlic, minced\n• 1 jalapeño, seeded and minced\n• 1 teaspoon ground cumin\n• 1 teaspoon dried oregano\n• 6 cups chicken broth\n• 2 tomatoes, diced\n• 1 bell pepper, diced\n• Juice of 3 limes\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• Fresh cilantro, chopped, for garnish\n• Avocado slices for serving\n• Tortilla strips or chips for topping\n• Lime wedges for serving</string>
    <string name="crock_pot_stuffing_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> In a large pot, heat olive oil over medium heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Add chopped onion, minced garlic, and minced jalapeño. Sauté until the onion is translucent.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Stir in shredded chicken, ground cumin, and dried oregano. Cook for 2-3 minutes to infuse the flavors.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Pour in chicken broth and bring the soup to a simmer.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Add diced tomatoes and bell pepper to the soup. Simmer for an additional 10-15 minutes until the vegetables are tender.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Stir in lime juice and season with salt and black pepper to taste.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Ladle the Chicken Lime Soup into bowls.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Garnish with chopped fresh cilantro, avocado slices, and tortilla strips or chips.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Serve the soup hot with lime wedges on the side.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Chicken Lime Soup is often served as a light and refreshing meal on its own or with a side of rice.]]></string>


    <!--    ##########  Cheesy Chicken Recipe-->

    <string name="golden_chicken_nuggets_title">Cheesy Chicken and Broccoli Casserole</string>
    <string name="golden_chicken_nuggets_time">40min</string>
    <string name="golden_chicken_nuggets_calories">77kcal</string>
    <string name="golden_chicken_nuggets_fats">3g</string>
    <string name="golden_chicken_nuggets_proteins">5g</string>
    <string name="golden_chicken_nuggets_ingredients">• 2 cups cooked and shredded chicken\n• 2 cups broccoli florets, blanched\n• 1 cup shredded cheddar cheese\n• 1 cup shredded mozzarella cheese\n• 1/2 cup grated Parmesan cheese\n• 1 cup mayonnaise\n• 1/2 cup sour cream\n• 1 teaspoon garlic powder\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1 cup breadcrumbs\n• 2 tablespoons melted butter</string>
    <string name="golden_chicken_nuggets_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Preheat the oven to 375°F (190°C).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> In a large bowl, combine shredded chicken, blanched broccoli, cheddar cheese, mozzarella cheese, Parmesan cheese, mayonnaise, sour cream, garlic powder, salt, and black pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Transfer the mixture to a greased baking dish.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> In a small bowl, mix breadcrumbs with melted butter. Sprinkle the breadcrumb mixture over the casserole.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Bake for 25-30 minutes or until the casserole is hot and bubbly, and the top is golden brown.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Allow it to cool for a few minutes before serving.]]></string>

    <string name="cajun_chicken_drumsticks_title"> Cheesy Chicken and Rice Casserole</string>
    <string name="cajun_chicken_drumsticks_time">50min</string>
    <string name="cajun_chicken_drumsticks_calories">173kcal</string>
    <string name="cajun_chicken_drumsticks_fats">13g</string>
    <string name="cajun_chicken_drumsticks_proteins">13g</string>
    <string name="cajun_chicken_drumsticks_ingredients">• 2 cups cooked and shredded chicken\n• 1 cup cooked white rice\n• 1 cup shredded cheddar cheese\n• 1 cup shredded Monterey Jack cheese\n• 1/2 cup diced bell peppers (assorted colors)\n• 1/2 cup diced onions\n• 1 cup sour cream\n• 1 can (10.5 oz) condensed cream of chicken soup\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1 cup crushed cornflakes\n• 2 tablespoons melted butter</string>
    <string name="cajun_chicken_drumsticks_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Preheat the oven to 350°F (175°C).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> In a large bowl, combine shredded chicken, cooked rice, cheddar cheese, Monterey Jack cheese, diced bell peppers, diced onions, sour cream, condensed cream of chicken soup, salt, and black pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Transfer the mixture to a greased baking dish.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> In a small bowl, mix crushed cornflakes with melted butter. Sprinkle the cornflake mixture over the casserole.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Bake for 30-35 minutes or until the casserole is hot and bubbly.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Allow it to cool for a few minutes before serving.]]></string>

    <string name="white_chicken_chili_title">Stuffed Cheesy Chicken</string>
    <string name="white_chicken_chili_time">50min</string>
    <string name="white_chicken_chili_calories">554kcal</string>
    <string name="white_chicken_chili_fats">9g</string>
    <string name="white_chicken_chili_proteins">53g</string>
    <string name="white_chicken_chili_ingredients">• 4 boneless, skinless chicken breasts\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1 cup shredded mozzarella cheese\n• 1/2 cup sun-dried tomatoes, chopped\n• 1/4 cup fresh basil, chopped\n• 4 ounces cream cheese, softened\n• 2 tablespoons olive oil\n• 2 cloves garlic, minced\n• 1 teaspoon Italian seasoning\n• 1/2 cup chicken broth\n• Fresh parsley for garnish</string>
    <string name="white_chicken_chili_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Preheat the oven to 375°F (190°C).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Make a pocket in each chicken breast by cutting a slit horizontally through the side, being careful not to cut all the way through.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Season the inside and outside of each chicken breast with salt and black pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> In a bowl, combine shredded mozzarella cheese, chopped sun-dried tomatoes, chopped fresh basil, and softened cream cheese.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Stuff each chicken breast with the cheese mixture, then secure the openings with toothpicks.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> In an oven-safe skillet, heat olive oil over medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Add minced garlic and sauté until fragrant.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Place the stuffed chicken breasts in the skillet and sear on each side until golden brown.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Sprinkle Italian seasoning over the chicken.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Pour chicken broth into the skillet, and transfer the skillet to the preheated oven.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 11:</b> Bake for 20-25 minutes or until the chicken is cooked through and the cheese is melted.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 12:</b> Garnish with fresh parsley before serving.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 13:</b> Stuffed Cheesy Chicken is often served with a side of vegetables, pasta, or rice.]]></string>

    <string name="chicken_shrimp_pasta_title">Cheesy Chicken Pasta Bake</string>
    <string name="chicken_shrimp_pasta_time">35min</string>
    <string name="chicken_shrimp_pasta_calories">643kcal</string>
    <string name="chicken_shrimp_pasta_fats">27g</string>
    <string name="chicken_shrimp_pasta_proteins">43g</string>
    <string name="chicken_shrimp_pasta_ingredients">• 8 oz (about 2 cups) penne or your favorite pasta, cooked al dente\n• 2 cups cooked and shredded chicken\n• 1 tablespoon olive oil\n• 1 onion, finely chopped\n• 2 cloves garlic, minced\n• 1 can (14 oz) diced tomatoes, drained\n• 1 can (10 oz) condensed cream of chicken soup\n• 1 cup sour cream\n• 1 cup shredded mozzarella cheese\n• 1/2 cup grated Parmesan cheese\n• 1 teaspoon dried Italian herbs\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• Fresh basil or parsley for garnish</string>
    <string name="chicken_shrimp_pasta_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Preheat the oven to 375°F (190°C).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> In a large skillet, heat olive oil over medium heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Add chopped onion and minced garlic. Sauté until the onion is translucent.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Add diced tomatoes and cook for an additional 2-3 minutes.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Stir in condensed cream of chicken soup and sour cream. Mix until well combined.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Add shredded chicken, cooked pasta, mozzarella cheese, grated Parmesan cheese, dried Italian herbs, salt, and black pepper. Mix until the ingredients are evenly distributed.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Transfer the mixture to a greased baking dish.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Bake in the preheated oven for 20-25 minutes or until the top is golden brown and bubbly.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Garnish with fresh basil or parsley before serving.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Cheesy Chicken Pasta Bake is often served on its own or with a side of garlic bread or a simple salad.]]></string>

    <string name="chicken_taco_casserole_title">Cheesy Chicken Enchiladas</string>
    <string name="chicken_taco_casserole_time">45min</string>
    <string name="chicken_taco_casserole_calories">638kcal</string>
    <string name="chicken_taco_casserole_fats">Chicken</string>
    <string name="chicken_taco_casserole_proteins">Chicken</string>
    <string name="chicken_taco_casserole_ingredients">• 2 cups cooked and shredded chicken\n• 1 tablespoon olive oil\n• 1 onion, finely chopped\n• 2 cloves garlic, minced\n• 1 can (14 oz) diced tomatoes, drained\n• 1 can (4 oz) diced green chilies\n• 1 teaspoon ground cumin\n• 1 teaspoon chili powder\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1 cup sour cream\n• 2 cups shredded Monterey Jack cheese\n• 1 cup shredded cheddar cheese\n• 1/4 cup fresh cilantro, chopped\n• 8 large flour tortillas\n• Enchilada sauce (store-bought or homemade)\n• Sliced green onions and diced tomatoes for garnish</string>
    <string name="chicken_taco_casserole_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Preheat the oven to 375°F (190°C).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> In a large skillet, heat olive oil over medium heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Add chopped onion and minced garlic. Sauté until the onion is translucent.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Stir in diced tomatoes, diced green chilies, ground cumin, chili powder, salt, and black pepper. Cook for an additional 2-3 minutes.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Add shredded chicken to the skillet and mix well. Remove from heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> In a bowl, combine sour cream, shredded Monterey Jack cheese, shredded cheddar cheese, and chopped cilantro.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Warm the flour tortillas.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Spread a spoonful of the cheese mixture onto each tortilla, followed by a portion of the chicken mixture.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Roll up the tortillas and place them seam-side down in a greased baking dish.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Pour enchilada sauce over the rolled tortillas, covering them evenly.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 11:</b> Sprinkle additional cheese on top if desired.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 12:</b> Bake in the preheated oven for 20-25 minutes or until the enchiladas are hot and bubbly.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 13:</b> Garnish with sliced green onions and diced tomatoes.]]></string>

    <string name="easy_balsamic_chicken_title">Cheesy Chicken Quesadillas</string>
    <string name="easy_balsamic_chicken_time">30min</string>
    <string name="easy_balsamic_chicken_calories">287.kcal</string>
    <string name="easy_balsamic_chicken_fats">15g</string>
    <string name="easy_balsamic_chicken_proteins">29g</string>
    <string name="easy_balsamic_chicken_ingredients">• 2 cups cooked and shredded chicken\n• 1 cup shredded cheddar cheese\n• 1 cup shredded Monterey Jack cheese\n• 1/2 cup diced red bell pepper\n• 1/2 cup diced green bell pepper\n• 1/4 cup chopped green onions\n• 1 teaspoon ground cumin\n• 1 teaspoon chili powder\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 8 large flour tortillas\n• 2 tablespoons butter\n• Salsa, guacamole, and sour cream for serving</string>
    <string name="easy_balsamic_chicken_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> In a large bowl, combine shredded chicken, cheddar cheese, Monterey Jack cheese, diced red bell pepper, diced green bell pepper, chopped green onions, ground cumin, chili powder, salt, and black pepper. Mix well.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Lay out four of the flour tortillas.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Divide the chicken and cheese mixture evenly among the four tortillas, spreading it over half of each tortilla.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Fold the other half of each tortilla over the filling, creating a half-moon shape.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> In a large skillet, melt 1 tablespoon of butter over medium heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Place two filled tortillas in the skillet and cook until the bottoms are golden brown and the cheese is melting, usually 2-3 minutes.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Flip the quesadillas and cook the other side until golden brown.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Repeat the process with the remaining quesadillas, adding more butter to the skillet as needed.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Once cooked, remove from the skillet and let them cool for a moment before slicing.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Serve the Cheesy Chicken Quesadillas with salsa, guacamole, and sour cream on the side.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 11:</b> Cheesy Chicken Quesadillas are often served as a delicious snack or as part of a casual meal.]]></string>

    <string name="roasted_balsamic_chicken_title">Cheesy Chicken Bruschetta</string>
    <string name="roasted_balsamic_chicken_time">1hr 15min</string>
    <string name="roasted_balsamic_chicken_calories">Roasted</string>
    <string name="roasted_balsamic_chicken_fats">Roasted</string>
    <string name="roasted_balsamic_chicken_proteins">Roasted</string>
    <string name="roasted_balsamic_chicken_ingredients">• 4 boneless, skinless chicken breasts\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1 tablespoon olive oil\n• 1 cup cherry tomatoes, halved\n• 1/2 cup fresh mozzarella cheese, diced\n• 1/4 cup grated Parmesan cheese\n• 1/4 cup fresh basil, chopped\n• 2 cloves garlic, minced\n• Balsamic glaze for drizzling\n• Baguette or Italian bread slices for serving</string>
    <string name="roasted_balsamic_chicken_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Preheat the oven to 375°F (190°C).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Season the chicken breasts with salt and black pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> In an oven-safe skillet, heat olive oil over medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Sear the chicken breasts on both sides until golden brown.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> In a bowl, combine halved cherry tomatoes, diced mozzarella cheese, grated Parmesan cheese, chopped fresh basil, and minced garlic.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Spoon the tomato and cheese mixture over each chicken breast.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Transfer the skillet to the preheated oven and bake for 20-25 minutes or until the chicken is cooked through and the cheese is melted and bubbly.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Remove from the oven and drizzle with balsamic glaze.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Serve the Cheesy Chicken Bruschetta on slices of baguette or Italian bread.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Cheesy Chicken Bruschetta is often served as a main dish alongside a salad or as an appetizer on toasted bread slices.]]></string>

    <string name="baked_chicken_teriyaki_title">Cheddar Chicken Bites</string>
    <string name="baked_chicken_teriyaki_time">28min</string>
    <string name="baked_chicken_teriyaki_calories">272kcal</string>
    <string name="baked_chicken_teriyaki_fats">10g</string>
    <string name="baked_chicken_teriyaki_proteins">25g</string>
    <string name="baked_chicken_teriyaki_ingredients">• 1 lb boneless, skinless chicken breasts, cut into bite-sized pieces\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1 cup sharp cheddar cheese, shredded\n• 1 cup breadcrumbs\n• 1 teaspoon garlic powder\n• 1 teaspoon onion powder\n• 1/2 teaspoon paprika\n• 2 eggs, beaten\n• Cooking spray or olive oil for baking</string>
    <string name="baked_chicken_teriyaki_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Preheat the oven to 400°F (200°C). Line a baking sheet with parchment paper or grease it with cooking spray.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> In a bowl, combine breadcrumbs, garlic powder, onion powder, paprika, salt, and black pepper. Mix well.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Dip each chicken bite into the beaten eggs, ensuring it\'s well-coated.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Roll the egg-coated chicken bite in the breadcrumb mixture, pressing gently to adhere the breadcrumbs.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Place the coated chicken bite on the prepared baking sheet.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Repeat the process for all chicken pieces.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Sprinkle shredded cheddar cheese over each chicken bite, pressing it down slightly.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Lightly spray the tops of the chicken bites with cooking spray or drizzle with a little olive oil.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Bake in the preheated oven for 15-20 minutes or until the chicken is cooked through, and the coating is golden brown and crispy.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Remove from the oven and let them cool for a few minutes before serving.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 11:</b> Cheddar Chicken Bites can be served as a delicious appetizer with your favorite dipping sauce or as a tasty addition to a salad.]]></string>

    <string name="grilled_teriyaki_chicken_title">Feta Stuffed Chicken</string>
    <string name="grilled_teriyaki_chicken_time">30min</string>
    <string name="grilled_teriyaki_chicken_calories">173kcal</string>
    <string name="grilled_teriyaki_chicken_fats">4g</string>
    <string name="grilled_teriyaki_chicken_proteins">32g</string>
    <string name="grilled_teriyaki_chicken_ingredients">• 4 boneless, skinless chicken breasts\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1 cup crumbled feta cheese\n• 1 cup spinach, chopped\n• 1/4 cup sun-dried tomatoes, chopped\n•  2 cloves garlic, minced\n• 1 tablespoon olive oil\n• 1 teaspoon dried oregano\n• 1 teaspoon dried thyme\n• 1 tablespoon lemon juice\n• Toothpicks or kitchen twine for securing</string>
    <string name="grilled_teriyaki_chicken_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Preheat the oven to 375°F (190°C).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Season the chicken breasts with salt and black pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> In a bowl, combine crumbled feta cheese, chopped spinach, chopped sun-dried tomatoes, minced garlic, olive oil, dried oregano, dried thyme, and lemon juice. Mix well.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Make a pocket in each chicken breast by cutting a slit horizontally through the side, being careful not to cut all the way through.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Stuff each chicken breast with the feta mixture, then secure the openings with toothpicks or tie with kitchen twine.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Season the outside of the chicken breasts with a bit more salt and black pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> In an oven-safe skillet, heat olive oil over medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Sear the stuffed chicken breasts on each side until golden brown.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Transfer the skillet to the preheated oven and bake for 20-25 minutes or until the chicken is cooked through.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Remove from the oven and let them rest for a few minutes before serving.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 11:</b>  Feta Stuffed Chicken is often served with a side of roasted vegetables, quinoa, or a fresh salad.]]></string>

    <string name="baked_chicken_fajitas_title">Authentic Chicken Parmesan</string>
    <string name="baked_chicken_fajitas_time">1hr 10min</string>
    <string name="baked_chicken_fajitas_calories">375kcal</string>
    <string name="baked_chicken_fajitas_fats">14g</string>
    <string name="baked_chicken_fajitas_proteins">22g</string>
    <string name="baked_chicken_fajitas_ingredients">• 4 boneless, skinless chicken breasts\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1 cup all-purpose flour\n• 2 large eggs\n• 2 cups breadcrumbs (preferably Italian-style)\n• 1 cup grated Parmesan cheese\n• 2 cups marinara sauce\n• 2 cups shredded mozzarella cheese\n• Fresh basil or parsley for garnish\n• Olive oil for frying</string>
    <string name="baked_chicken_fajitas_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Preheat the oven to 375°F (190°C).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Season the chicken breasts with salt and black pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Set up a breading station: Place the flour in one shallow dish, beat the eggs in another dish, and mix the breadcrumbs with grated Parmesan cheese in a third dish.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Dredge each chicken breast in the flour, shaking off any excess.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Dip the floured chicken in the beaten eggs, ensuring it\'s well-coated.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Press the chicken into the breadcrumb and Parmesan mixture, ensuring an even coating. Repeat for all chicken breasts.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> In a large skillet, heat olive oil over medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Fry the breaded chicken breasts until golden brown on both sides. This step is to give the chicken a crisp exterior; it doesn\'t need to cook through as it will finish in the oven.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> In a baking dish, spread a thin layer of marinara sauce.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Place the fried chicken breasts in the baking dish.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 11:</b> Spoon additional marinara sauce over each chicken breast.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 12:</b> Sprinkle shredded mozzarella cheese over the top.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 13:</b> Bake in the preheated oven for 25-30 minutes or until the chicken is cooked through, and the cheese is melted and bubbly.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 14:</b> Garnish with fresh basil or parsley before serving.]]></string>

    <string name="best_chicken_fajitas_title">Slow cooker Cheesy Chicken</string>
    <string name="best_chicken_fajitas_time">7hr 10min</string>
    <string name="best_chicken_fajitas_calories">480kcal</string>
    <string name="best_chicken_fajitas_fats">29g</string>
    <string name="best_chicken_fajitas_proteins">36g</string>
    <string name="best_chicken_fajitas_ingredients">• 4 boneless, skinless chicken breasts\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1 teaspoon garlic powder\n• 1 teaspoon onion powder\n• 1 teaspoon dried oregano\n• 1 teaspoon dried basil\n• 1/2 teaspoon dried thyme\n• 1 can (10.5 oz) condensed cream of chicken soup\n• 1/2 cup chicken broth\n• 1 cup shredded cheddar cheese\n• 1 cup shredded mozzarella cheese\n• 1/2 cup grated Parmesan cheese\n• 1/2 cup sour cream\n• Fresh parsley for garnish</string>
    <string name="best_chicken_fajitas_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Season the chicken breasts with salt, black pepper, garlic powder, onion powder, dried oregano, dried basil, and dried thyme.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Place the seasoned chicken breasts in the slow cooker.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> In a bowl, mix condensed cream of chicken soup with chicken broth. Pour the mixture over the chicken.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Cover the slow cooker and cook on low for 4-6 hours or until the chicken is cooked through and tender.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> About 30 minutes before serving, shred the chicken using two forks.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Stir in shredded cheddar cheese, shredded mozzarella cheese, grated Parmesan cheese, and sour cream. Mix well.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Cover and continue cooking on low for an additional 20-30 minutes or until the cheeses are melted and the mixture is creamy.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Garnish with fresh parsley before serving.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Slow Cooker Cheesy Chicken can be served over cooked rice, pasta, or with your favorite side dishes.]]></string>

    <string name="chili_chicken_fajitas_title">Chicken Breasts with Cheese Sauce</string>
    <string name="chili_chicken_fajitas_time">35min</string>
    <string name="chili_chicken_fajitas_calories">411kcal</string>
    <string name="chili_chicken_fajitas_fats">15g</string>
    <string name="chili_chicken_fajitas_proteins">21g</string>
    <string name="chili_chicken_fajitas_ingredients">• 4 boneless, skinless chicken breasts\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1 tablespoon olive oil\n• 1 teaspoon garlic powder\n• 1 teaspoon onion powder\n• 1 teaspoon dried thyme\n• 1 cup shredded cheddar cheese\n• 1/2 cup shredded mozzarella cheese\n• 1/4 cup grated Parmesan cheese\n• 1 cup milk\n• 2 tablespoons unsalted butter\n• 2 tablespoons all-purpose flour\n• Fresh parsley for garnish</string>
    <string name="chili_chicken_fajitas_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Preheat the oven to 375°F (190°C).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Season the chicken breasts with salt, black pepper, garlic powder, onion powder, and dried thyme.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> In an oven-safe skillet, heat olive oil over medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Sear the chicken breasts on both sides until golden brown.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Transfer the skillet to the preheated oven and bake for 20-25 minutes or until the chicken is cooked through.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> While the chicken is baking, prepare the cheese sauce. In a saucepan, melt butter over medium heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Add flour and whisk continuously to create a roux. Cook for 1-2 minutes until it becomes lightly golden.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Gradually pour in the milk, whisking constantly to avoid lumps.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Continue cooking and whisking until the sauce thickens.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Reduce heat to low, then stir in shredded cheddar cheese, shredded mozzarella cheese, and grated Parmesan cheese. Mix until the cheeses are melted and the sauce is smooth.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 11:</b> Season the cheese sauce with additional salt and black pepper to taste.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 12:</b> Once the chicken is done, spoon the cheese sauce over the chicken breasts.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 13:</b> Garnish with fresh parsley before serving.]]></string>


    <!--    ##########  Sweet Chicken Recipe-->

    <string name="coconut_lime_chicken_title">Coconut Lime Chicken</string>
    <string name="coconut_lime_chicken_time">50min</string>
    <string name="coconut_lime_chicken_calories">77kcal</string>
    <string name="coconut_lime_chicken_fats">3g</string>
    <string name="coconut_lime_chicken_proteins">5g</string>
    <string name="coconut_lime_chicken_ingredients">• 4 boneless, skinless chicken breasts\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1 cup coconut milk\n• Zest and juice of 2 limes\n• 3 tablespoons soy sauce\n• 2 tablespoons honey\n• 2 tablespoons coconut oil\n• 2 cloves garlic, minced\n• 1 teaspoon ginger, grated\n• Fresh cilantro for garnish\n• Lime wedges for serving</string>
    <string name="coconut_lime_chicken_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Season the chicken breasts with salt and black pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> In a bowl, whisk together coconut milk, lime zest, lime juice, soy sauce, and honey. Set aside.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> In a large skillet, heat coconut oil over medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Sear the chicken breasts on both sides until golden brown.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Lower the heat to medium, add minced garlic and grated ginger to the skillet. Sauté for about 1-2 minutes until fragrant.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Pour the coconut lime sauce over the chicken in the skillet.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Simmer for 15-20 minutes or until the chicken is cooked through and the sauce has thickened.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Garnish with fresh cilantro.Serve the Coconut Lime Chicken over rice or with your favorite side dish.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b>  You can optionally marinate the chicken in a portion of the coconut lime sauce for a few hours before cooking for enhanced flavor.]]></string>

    <string name="honey_glazed_chicken_title">Honey Glazed Chicken</string>
    <string name="honey_glazed_chicken_time">40min</string>
    <string name="honey_glazed_chicken_calories">77kcal</string>
    <string name="honey_glazed_chicken_fats">3g</string>
    <string name="honey_glazed_chicken_proteins">5g</string>
    <string name="honey_glazed_chicken_ingredients">• 4 boneless, skinless chicken breasts\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1/4 cup honey\n• 2 tablespoons soy sauce\n• 1 tablespoon Dijon mustard\n• 1 tablespoon olive oil\n• 2 cloves garlic, minced\n• 1 teaspoon fresh ginger, grated\n• Sesame seeds and chopped green onions for garnish</string>
    <string name="honey_glazed_chicken_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Season the chicken breasts with salt and black pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> In a bowl, whisk together honey, soy sauce, Dijon mustard, minced garlic, and grated ginger to create the glaze. Set aside a portion for later.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Heat olive oil in a skillet over medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Sear the chicken breasts on both sides until golden brown.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Pour the honey glaze over the chicken in the skillet, coating each piece evenly.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Lower the heat to medium and continue cooking for 15-20 minutes or until the chicken is cooked through and the glaze has thickened.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Baste the chicken with the glaze occasionally during cooking.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Garnish with sesame seeds and chopped green onions.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Drizzle the reserved honey glaze over the chicken just before serving.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Serve the Honey Glazed Chicken with rice or your favorite side dish.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 11:</b> You can optionally marinate the chicken in a portion of the honey glaze for a few hours before cooking for enhanced flavor.]]></string>

    <string name="apricot_glazed_chicken_title">Apricot Glazed Chicken</string>
    <string name="apricot_glazed_chicken_time">35min</string>
    <string name="apricot_glazed_chicken_calories">77kcal</string>
    <string name="apricot_glazed_chicken_fats">3g</string>
    <string name="apricot_glazed_chicken_proteins">5g</string>
    <string name="apricot_glazed_chicken_ingredients">• 4 boneless, skinless chicken breasts\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1 cup apricot preserves\n• 2 tablespoons Dijon mustard\n• 2 tablespoons soy sauce\n• 2 tablespoons olive oil\n• 2 cloves garlic, minced\n• 1 teaspoon fresh thyme leaves\n• Chopped fresh parsley for garnish</string>
    <string name="apricot_glazed_chicken_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Season the chicken breasts with salt and black pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b>In a small bowl, whisk together apricot preserves, Dijon mustard, soy sauce, minced garlic, and fresh thyme leaves to create the glaze.Heat olive oil in a skillet over medium-high heat. <br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Sear the chicken breasts on both sides until golden brown.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b>Pour the apricot glaze over the chicken in the skillet, coating each piece evenly. <br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Lower the heat to medium and continue cooking for 15-20 minutes or until the chicken is cooked through and the glaze has thickened.Baste the chicken with the glaze occasionally during cooking.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Garnish with chopped fresh parsley.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Serve the Apricot Glazed Chicken with rice or your favorite side dish.]]></string>

    <string name="honey_chicken_thighs_title">Honey Chicken Thighs</string>
    <string name="honey_chicken_thighs_time">1hr</string>
    <string name="honey_chicken_thighs_calories">77kcal</string>
    <string name="honey_chicken_thighs_fats">3g</string>
    <string name="honey_chicken_thighs_proteins">5g</string>
    <string name="honey_chicken_thighs_ingredients">• 4-6 bone-in, skin-on chicken thighs\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1/4 cup honey\n• 2 tablespoons soy sauce\n• 1 tablespoon olive oil\n• 2 cloves garlic, minced\n• 1 teaspoon fresh ginger, grated\n• Sesame seeds and chopped green onions for garnish</string>
    <string name="honey_chicken_thighs_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Preheat the oven to 400°F (200°C).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Pat the chicken thighs dry with paper towels and season with salt and black pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> In a small bowl, whisk together honey, soy sauce, minced garlic, and grated ginger.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Heat olive oil in an oven-safe skillet over medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Sear the chicken thighs, skin side down, until golden brown.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Flip the chicken thighs and pour the honey glaze over them, coating each piece evenly.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Transfer the skillet to the preheated oven.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Roast for 20-25 minutes or until the chicken thighs are cooked through and the skin is crispy.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Baste the chicken with the glaze halfway through cooking.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Garnish with sesame seeds and chopped green onions.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 11:</b>Serve the Honey Glazed Chicken Thighs with rice or your favorite side dish. ]]></string>

    <string name="orange_rosemary_chicken_title">Orange and Rosemary Chicken</string>
    <string name="orange_rosemary_chicken_time">40min</string>
    <string name="orange_rosemary_chicken_calories">77kcal</string>
    <string name="orange_rosemary_chicken_fats">3g</string>
    <string name="orange_rosemary_chicken_proteins">5g</string>
    <string name="orange_rosemary_chicken_ingredients">• 4 bone-in, skin-on chicken thighs\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• Zest and juice of 2 oranges\n• 2 tablespoons olive oil\n• 3 cloves garlic, minced\n• 1 tablespoon fresh rosemary, chopped\n• 1 tablespoon honey\n• Orange slices and fresh rosemary sprigs for garnish</string>
    <string name="orange_rosemary_chicken_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Preheat the oven to 375°F (190°C).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Pat the chicken thighs dry with paper towels and season with salt and black pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> In a bowl, whisk together orange zest, orange juice, olive oil, minced garlic, chopped rosemary, and honey.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Place the chicken thighs in a baking dish.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Pour the orange and rosemary mixture over the chicken, coating each piece evenly.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Marinate the chicken in the refrigerator for at least 30 minutes, or overnight for more flavor.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Bake in the preheated oven for 35-40 minutes or until the chicken is cooked through and the skin is golden brown.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Baste the chicken with the marinade halfway through cooking.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Garnish with orange slices and fresh rosemary sprigs.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Serve the Orange and Rosemary Chicken with roasted vegetables or your favorite side dish.]]></string>

    <string name="honey_sriacha_chicken_leg_title">Honey Sriacha Chicken Legs</string>
    <string name="honey_sriacha_chicken_leg_time">1hr 25min</string>
    <string name="honey_sriacha_chicken_leg_calories">77kcal</string>
    <string name="honey_sriacha_chicken_leg_fats">3g</string>
    <string name="honey_sriacha_chicken_leg_proteins">5g</string>
    <string name="honey_sriacha_chicken_leg_ingredients">• 4-6 chicken drumsticks or chicken legs\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1/4 cup honey\n• 2 tablespoons Sriracha sauce (adjust to taste)\n• 2 tablespoons soy sauce\n• 1 tablespoon olive oil\n• 2 cloves garlic, mincedSesame seeds and chopped green onions for garnish</string>
    <string name="honey_sriacha_chicken_leg_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Preheat the oven to 400°F (200°C).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Pat the chicken legs dry with paper towels and season with salt and black pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> In a bowl, whisk together honey, Sriracha sauce, soy sauce, olive oil, and minced garlic.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Place the chicken legs in a baking dish.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Pour the honey Sriracha mixture over the chicken legs, coating each piece evenly.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Marinate the chicken in the refrigerator for at least 30 minutes, or longer for more flavor.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Bake in the preheated oven for 40-45 minutes or until the chicken is cooked through, and the skin is crispy.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Baste the chicken with the sauce halfway through cooking.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Garnish with sesame seeds and chopped green onions.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Serve the Honey Sriracha Chicken Legs with rice or your favorite side dish.]]></string>

    <string name="baked_honey_garlic_chicken_title">Baked Honey Garlic Chicken</string>
    <string name="baked_honey_garlic_chicken_time">30min</string>
    <string name="baked_honey_garlic_chicken_calories">77kcal</string>
    <string name="baked_honey_garlic_chicken_fats">3g</string>
    <string name="baked_honey_garlic_chicken_proteins">5g</string>
    <string name="baked_honey_garlic_chicken_ingredients">• 4 boneless, skinless chicken breasts\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1/2 cup honey\n• 1/4 cup soy sauce\n• 3 tablespoons ketchup\n• 2 tablespoons olive oil\n• 3 cloves garlic, minced\n• 1 teaspoon fresh ginger, grated\n• Sesame seeds and chopped green onions for garnish</string>
    <string name="baked_honey_garlic_chicken_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Preheat the oven to 375°F (190°C).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Season the chicken breasts with salt and black pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> In a bowl, whisk together honey, soy sauce, ketchup, olive oil, minced garlic, and grated ginger.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Place the chicken breasts in a baking dish.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Pour the honey garlic mixture over the chicken, coating each piece evenly.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Bake in the preheated oven for 25-30 minutes or until the chicken is cooked through.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Baste the chicken with the sauce halfway through baking.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Garnish with sesame seeds and chopped green onions.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Serve the Baked Honey Garlic Chicken with rice or your favorite side dish.]]></string>

    <string name="fig_glazed_chicken_title">Fig Glazed Chicken</string>
    <string name="fig_glazed_chicken_time">50min</string>
    <string name="fig_glazed_chicken_calories">77kcal</string>
    <string name="fig_glazed_chicken_fats">3g</string>
    <string name="fig_glazed_chicken_proteins">5g</string>
    <string name="fig_glazed_chicken_ingredients">• 4 bone-in, skin-on chicken thighs\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1/2 cup fig preserves\n• 2 tablespoons balsamic vinegar\n• 1 tablespoon soy sauce\n• 1 tablespoon olive oil\n• 2 cloves garlic, minced\n• 1 teaspoon fresh rosemary, chopped\n• Fresh figs for garnish (optional)\n• Chopped fresh parsley for garnish</string>
    <string name="fig_glazed_chicken_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Preheat the oven to 375°F (190°C).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Pat the chicken thighs dry with paper towels and season with salt and black pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> In a bowl, whisk together fig preserves, balsamic vinegar, soy sauce, olive oil, minced garlic, and chopped rosemary.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Place the chicken thighs in a baking dish.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Pour the fig glaze over the chicken, coating each piece evenly.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Bake in the preheated oven for 35-40 minutes or until the chicken is cooked through, and the skin is golden brown.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Baste the chicken with the glaze halfway through baking.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Garnish with fresh figs (if using) and chopped fresh parsley.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Serve the Fig Glazed Chicken with couscous or your favorite side dish.]]></string>

    <string name="honey_sesame_chicken_title">Honey Sesame Chicken</string>
    <string name="honey_sesame_chicken_time">35min</string>
    <string name="honey_sesame_chicken_calories">77kcal</string>
    <string name="honey_sesame_chicken_fats">3g</string>
    <string name="honey_sesame_chicken_proteins">5g</string>
    <string name="honey_sesame_chicken_ingredients">• 4 boneless, skinless chicken breasts, cut into bite-sized pieces\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1/4 cup honey\n• 2 tablespoons soy sauce\n• 1 tablespoon sesame oil\n• 1 tablespoon rice vinegar\n• 2 cloves garlic, minced\n• 1 teaspoon fresh ginger, grated\n• 1 tablespoon cornstarch\n• 2 tablespoons water\n• Sesame seeds and chopped green onions for garnish\n• Cooked white or brown rice for serving</string>
    <string name="honey_sesame_chicken_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Season the chicken pieces with salt and black pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> In a bowl, whisk together honey, soy sauce, sesame oil, rice vinegar, minced garlic, and grated ginger.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> In a small bowl, mix cornstarch with water to create a slurry.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Heat a large skillet or wok over medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Add the chicken pieces and cook until browned on all sides and cooked through.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Pour the honey sesame sauce over the cooked chicken and toss to coat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Stir in the cornstarch slurry and cook until the sauce thickens.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Garnish with sesame seeds and chopped green onions.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Serve the Honey Sesame Chicken over cooked rice.]]></string>

    <string name="mango_chili_chicken_title">Mango Chili Lime Chicken</string>
    <string name="mango_chili_chicken_time">40min</string>
    <string name="mango_chili_chicken_calories">77kcal</string>
    <string name="mango_chili_chicken_fats">3g</string>
    <string name="mango_chili_chicken_proteins">5g</string>
    <string name="mango_chili_chicken_ingredients">• 4 boneless, skinless chicken breasts\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1 ripe mango, peeled and diced\n• 2 tablespoons chili powder\n• Juice and zest of 2 limes\n• 2 tablespoons honey\n• 1 tablespoon olive oil\n• 2 cloves garlic, minced\n• Fresh cilantro for garnish\n• Sliced jalapeños for extra heat (optional)</string>
    <string name="mango_chili_chicken_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Season the chicken breasts with salt and black pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> In a blender or food processor, combine diced mango, chili powder, lime juice, lime zest, honey, olive oil, and minced garlic. Blend until smooth.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Reserve a portion of the mango mixture for later use.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Marinate the chicken breasts in the remaining mango mixture for at least 30 minutes, or refrigerate for several hours for enhanced flavor.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Preheat the grill or a grill pan over medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Grill the chicken breasts for 6-8 minutes per side or until fully cooked, basting with the reserved mango mixture during the last few minutes of grilling.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Garnish with fresh cilantro and sliced jalapeños if desired.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Serve the Mango Chili Lime Chicken with rice or your favorite side dish.]]></string>

    <!--    ##########   Chicken Kiev Recipe-->


    <string name="baked_chicken_kiev_title">Baked Chicken Kiev</string>
    <string name="baked_chicken_kiev_time">1hr 35min</string>
    <string name="baked_chicken_kiev_calories">77kcal</string>
    <string name="baked_chicken_kiev_fats">3g</string>
    <string name="baked_chicken_kiev_proteins">5g</string>
    <string name="baked_chicken_kiev_ingredients">• 4 boneless, skinless chicken breasts\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1 cup breadcrumbs (preferably seasoned)\n• 1/2 cup grated Parmesan cheese\n• 1/2 cup unsalted butter, softened\n• 2 tablespoons fresh parsley, chopped\n• 2 cloves garlic, minced\n• 1 teaspoon lemon zest\n• 1 tablespoon lemon juice\n• 2 eggs, beaten\n• Olive oil or cooking spray for baking</string>
    <string name="baked_chicken_kiev_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Preheat the oven to 400°F (200°C). Grease a baking sheet with olive oil or cooking spray.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Season the chicken breasts with salt and black pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> In a bowl, combine breadcrumbs and grated Parmesan cheese.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> In another bowl, mix together softened butter, chopped parsley, minced garlic, lemon zest, and lemon juice.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Place each chicken breast between plastic wrap and pound with a meat mallet to flatten slightly.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Spread a generous portion of the garlic butter mixture over each chicken breast.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Roll the chicken breasts tightly, sealing the edges, to form a log or cylinder shape.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Dip each rolled chicken breast into the beaten eggs, ensuring it\'s fully coated.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Roll the egg-coated chicken in the breadcrumb and Parmesan mixture, pressing the breadcrumbs onto the chicken to adhere.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Place the coated chicken breasts on the prepared baking sheet.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 11:</b> Bake in the preheated oven for 25-30 minutes or until the chicken is golden brown and cooked through.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 12:</b> Allow the Baked Chicken Kiev to rest for a few minutes before serving.]]></string>

    <string name="authentic_chicken_parmesan_title">Authentic Chicken Parmesan</string>
    <string name="authentic_chicken_parmesan_time">1hr 10min</string>
    <string name="authentic_chicken_parmesan_calories">77kcal</string>
    <string name="authentic_chicken_parmesan_fats">3g</string>
    <string name="authentic_chicken_parmesan_proteins">5g</string>
    <string name="authentic_chicken_parmesan_ingredients">• 4 boneless, skinless chicken breasts\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1 cup all-purpose flour\n• 2 large eggs, beaten\n• 1 cup breadcrumbs (preferably Italian seasoned)\n• 1 cup grated Parmesan cheese\n• 1 cup marinara sauce\n• 1 cup shredded mozzarella cheese\n• 1/4 cup fresh basil, chopped\n• Olive oil for frying</string>
    <string name="authentic_chicken_parmesan_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Preheat the oven to 375°F (190°C).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Season the chicken breasts with salt and black pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Dredge each chicken breast in flour, shaking off excess.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Dip the floured chicken into the beaten eggs, ensuring it\'s fully coated.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> In a separate bowl, combine breadcrumbs and grated Parmesan cheese.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Coat each chicken breast with the breadcrumb mixture, pressing the crumbs onto the chicken to adhere.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Heat olive oil in a large skillet over medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Fry the breaded chicken breasts until golden brown on both sides and cooked through (about 4-5 minutes per side).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Transfer the fried chicken to a baking dish.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Spoon marinara sauce over each chicken breast.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 11:</b> Sprinkle shredded mozzarella cheese over the sauce.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 12:</b> Bake in the preheated oven for 20-25 minutes or until the cheese is melted and bubbly.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 13:</b> Garnish with chopped fresh basil before serving.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 14:</b> Authentic Chicken Parmesan is often served over spaghetti or your favorite pasta.]]></string>

    <string name="classic_chicken_kiev_title">Classic Chicken Kiev</string>
    <string name="classic_chicken_kiev_time">55min</string>
    <string name="classic_chicken_kiev_calories">77kcal</string>
    <string name="classic_chicken_kiev_fats">3g</string>
    <string name="classic_chicken_kiev_proteins">5g</string>
    <string name="classic_chicken_kiev_ingredients">• 4 boneless, skinless chicken breasts\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1 cup unsalted butter, softened\n• 2 tablespoons fresh parsley, chopped\n• 2 cloves garlic, minced\n• 1 teaspoon lemon zest\n• 1 tablespoon lemon juice\n• 1 cup all-purpose flour\n• 2 large eggs, beaten\n• 1 cup breadcrumbs (preferably fresh)\n• Olive oil for frying</string>
    <string name="classic_chicken_kiev_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Preheat the oven to 375°F (190°C).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Season the chicken breasts with salt and black pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> In a bowl, combine softened butter, chopped parsley, minced garlic, lemon zest, and lemon juice. Mix well to create the garlic herb butter.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Lay out a sheet of plastic wrap. Spoon the garlic herb butter onto the plastic wrap and roll it into a log or cylinder shape. Place it in the freezer to firm up.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Flatten each chicken breast slightly with a meat mallet.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Remove the garlic herb butter log from the freezer and slice it into 4 equal portions.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Place one portion of the garlic herb butter in the center of each chicken breast.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Fold the sides of the chicken breast over the butter and roll it tightly, sealing the edges to form a log or cylinder shape.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Dredge each chicken breast in flour, shaking off excess.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Dip the floured chicken into the beaten eggs, ensuring it\'s fully coated.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 11:</b> Coat each chicken breast with breadcrumbs, pressing the crumbs onto the chicken to adhere.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 12:</b> Heat olive oil in a large skillet over medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 13:</b> Fry the breaded chicken until golden brown on all sides (about 2-3 minutes per side).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 14:</b> Transfer the fried chicken to a baking dish.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 15:</b> Bake in the preheated oven for 20-25 minutes or until the chicken is cooked through.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 16:</b> Serve the Classic Chicken Kiev with your favorite side dishes.]]></string>

    <string name="garlic_hub_kiev_title">Garlic Herb Chicken Kiev</string>
    <string name="garlic_hub_kiev_time">50min</string>
    <string name="garlic_hub_kiev_calories">77kcal</string>
    <string name="garlic_hub_kiev_fats">3g</string>
    <string name="garlic_hub_kiev_proteins">5g</string>
    <string name="garlic_hub_kiev_ingredients">• 4 boneless, skinless chicken breasts\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1 cup unsalted butter, softened\n• 3 tablespoons fresh parsley, finely chopped\n• 2 cloves garlic, minced\n• 1 teaspoon dried thyme\n• 1 teaspoon dried rosemary\n• 1 cup all-purpose flour\n• 2 large eggs, beaten\n• 1 cup breadcrumbs (preferably fresh)\n• Olive oil for frying</string>
    <string name="garlic_hub_kiev_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Preheat the oven to 375°F (190°C).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Season the chicken breasts with salt and black pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> In a bowl, combine softened butter, chopped parsley, minced garlic, dried thyme, and dried rosemary. Mix well to create the garlic herb butter.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Flatten each chicken breast slightly with a meat mallet.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Place a generous portion of the garlic herb butter in the center of each chicken breast.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Fold the sides of the chicken breast over the butter and roll it tightly, sealing the edges to form a log or cylinder shape.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Dredge each chicken breast in flour, shaking off excess.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Dip the floured chicken into the beaten eggs, ensuring it\'s fully coated.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Coat each chicken breast with breadcrumbs, pressing the crumbs onto the chicken to adhere.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Heat olive oil in a large skillet over medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 11:</b> Fry the breaded chicken until golden brown on all sides (about 2-3 minutes per side).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 12:</b> Transfer the fried chicken to a baking dish.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 13:</b> Bake in the preheated oven for 20-25 minutes or until the chicken is cooked through.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 14:</b> Serve the Garlic Herb Chicken Kiev with your favorite side dishes.]]></string>

    <string name="lemon_butter_kiev_title">Lemon Butter Chicken Kiev</string>
    <string name="lemon_butter_kiev_time">1hr</string>
    <string name="lemon_butter_kiev_calories">77kcal</string>
    <string name="lemon_butter_kiev_fats">3g</string>
    <string name="lemon_butter_kiev_proteins">5g</string>
    <string name="lemon_butter_kiev_ingredients">• 4 boneless, skinless chicken breasts\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1 cup unsalted butter, softened\n• 3 tablespoons fresh parsley, chopped\n• 2 cloves garlic, minced\n• Zest of 1 lemon\n• 1 tablespoon lemon juice\n• 1 cup all-purpose flour\n• 2 large eggs, beaten\n• 1 cup breadcrumbs (preferably fresh)\n• Olive oil for frying</string>
    <string name="lemon_butter_kiev_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Preheat the oven to 375°F (190°C).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Season the chicken breasts with salt and black pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> In a bowl, combine softened butter, chopped parsley, minced garlic, lemon zest, and lemon juice. Mix well to create the lemon butter mixture.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Flatten each chicken breast slightly with a meat mallet.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Place a generous portion of the lemon butter mixture in the center of each chicken breast.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Fold the sides of the chicken breast over the butter and roll it tightly, sealing the edges to form a log or cylinder shape.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Dredge each chicken breast in flour, shaking off excess.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Dip the floured chicken into the beaten eggs, ensuring it\'s fully coated.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Coat each chicken breast with breadcrumbs, pressing the crumbs onto the chicken to adhere.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Heat olive oil in a large skillet over medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 11:</b> Fry the breaded chicken until golden brown on all sides (about 2-3 minutes per side).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 12:</b> Transfer the fried chicken to a baking dish.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 13:</b> Bake in the preheated oven for 20-25 minutes or until the chicken is cooked through.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 14:</b> Serve the Lemon Butter Chicken Kiev with your favorite side dishes.]]></string>

    <string name="teriyaki_chicken_kiev_title">Teriyaki Chicken Kiev</string>
    <string name="teriyaki_chicken_kiev_time">1hr</string>
    <string name="teriyaki_chicken_kiev_calories">77kcal</string>
    <string name="teriyaki_chicken_kiev_fats">3g</string>
    <string name="teriyaki_chicken_kiev_proteins">5g</string>
    <string name="teriyaki_chicken_kiev_ingredients">• 4 boneless, skinless chicken breasts\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1 cup unsalted butter, softened\n• 3 tablespoons soy sauce\n• 2 tablespoons honey\n• 2 cloves garlic, minced\n• 1 teaspoon fresh ginger, grated\n• 1 cup all-purpose flour\n• 2 large eggs, beaten\n• 1 cup breadcrumbs (preferably Japanese-style panko)\n• Olive oil for frying</string>
    <string name="teriyaki_chicken_kiev_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Preheat the oven to 375°F (190°C).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Season the chicken breasts with salt and black pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> In a bowl, combine softened butter, soy sauce, honey, minced garlic, and grated ginger. Mix well to create the teriyaki butter mixture.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Flatten each chicken breast slightly with a meat mallet.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Place a generous portion of the teriyaki butter mixture in the center of each chicken breast.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Fold the sides of the chicken breast over the butter and roll it tightly, sealing the edges to form a log or cylinder shape.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Dredge each chicken breast in flour, shaking off excess.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Dip the floured chicken into the beaten eggs, ensuring it\'s fully coated.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Coat each chicken breast with breadcrumbs, pressing the crumbs onto the chicken to adhere.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Heat olive oil in a large skillet over medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 11:</b> Fry the breaded chicken until golden brown on all sides (about 2-3 minutes per side).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 12:</b> Transfer the fried chicken to a baking dish.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 13:</b> Bake in the preheated oven for 20-25 minutes or until the chicken is cooked through.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 14:</b> Serve the Teriyaki Chicken Kiev with steamed rice or your favorite side dishes.]]></string>

    <string name="mushroom_swiss_kiev_title">Mushroom and Swiss Chicken Kiev</string>
    <string name="mushroom_swiss_kiev_time">1hr 10min</string>
    <string name="mushroom_swiss_kiev_calories">77kcal</string>
    <string name="mushroom_swiss_kiev_fats">3g</string>
    <string name="mushroom_swiss_kiev_proteins">5g</string>
    <string name="mushroom_swiss_kiev_ingredients">• 4 boneless, skinless chicken breasts\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1 cup unsalted butter, softened\n• 1 cup button mushrooms, finely chopped\n• 1 cup Swiss cheese, shredded\n• 2 tablespoons fresh parsley, chopped\n• 1 cup all-purpose flour\n• 2 large eggs, beaten\n• 1 cup breadcrumbs (preferably fresh or panko)\n• Olive oil for frying</string>
    <string name="mushroom_swiss_kiev_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Preheat the oven to 375°F (190°C).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Season the chicken breasts with salt and black pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> In a bowl, combine softened butter, finely chopped mushrooms, shredded Swiss cheese, and chopped parsley. Mix well to create the mushroom Swiss filling.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Flatten each chicken breast slightly with a meat mallet.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Place a generous portion of the mushroom Swiss filling in the center of each chicken breast.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Fold the sides of the chicken breast over the filling and roll it tightly, sealing the edges to form a log or cylinder shape.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Dredge each chicken breast in flour, shaking off excess.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Dip the floured chicken into the beaten eggs, ensuring it\'s fully coated.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Coat each chicken breast with breadcrumbs, pressing the crumbs onto the chicken to adhere.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Heat olive oil in a large skillet over medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 11:</b> Fry the breaded chicken until golden brown on all sides (about 2-3 minutes per side).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 12:</b> Transfer the fried chicken to a baking dish.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 13:</b> Bake in the preheated oven for 20-25 minutes or until the chicken is cooked through.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 14:</b> Serve the Mushroom Swiss Chicken Kiev with a side of mashed potatoes or your favorite side dishes.]]></string>

    <string name="bacon_wrapped_kiev_title">Bacon-Wrapped Chicken Kiev</string>
    <string name="bacon_wrapped_kiev_time">55min</string>
    <string name="bacon_wrapped_kiev_calories">77kcal</string>
    <string name="bacon_wrapped_kiev_fats">3g</string>
    <string name="bacon_wrapped_kiev_proteins">5g</string>
    <string name="bacon_wrapped_kiev_ingredients">• 4 boneless, skinless chicken breasts\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1 cup unsalted butter, softened\n• 3 tablespoons fresh parsley, chopped\n• 2 cloves garlic, minced\n• 1 cup all-purpose flour\n• 2 large eggs, beaten\n• 1 cup breadcrumbs (preferably fresh or panko)\n• 8 slices bacon</string>
    <string name="bacon_wrapped_kiev_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Preheat the oven to 375°F (190°C).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Season the chicken breasts with salt and black pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> In a bowl, combine softened butter, chopped parsley, and minced garlic. Mix well to create the garlic herb butter.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Flatten each chicken breast slightly with a meat mallet.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Place a generous portion of the garlic herb butter in the center of each chicken breast.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Fold the sides of the chicken breast over the butter and roll it tightly, sealing the edges to form a log or cylinder shape.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Wrap each chicken breast with 2 slices of bacon, ensuring they are secure.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Dredge each bacon-wrapped chicken breast in flour, shaking off excess.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Dip the floured chicken into the beaten eggs, ensuring it\'s fully coated.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Coat each chicken breast with breadcrumbs, pressing the crumbs onto the chicken to adhere.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 11:</b> Heat olive oil in a large skillet over medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 12:</b> Fry the bacon-wrapped chicken until the bacon is crispy on all sides (about 2-3 minutes per side).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 13:</b> Transfer the bacon-wrapped chicken to a baking dish.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 14:</b> Bake in the preheated oven for 20-25 minutes or until the chicken is cooked through.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 15:</b> Serve the Bacon-Wrapped Chicken Kiev with your favorite side dishes.]]></string>

    <string name="dijon_mustard_kiev_title">Dijon Mustard Chicken Kiev</string>
    <string name="dijon_mustard_kiev_time">1hr 10min</string>
    <string name="dijon_mustard_kiev_calories">77kcal</string>
    <string name="dijon_mustard_kiev_fats">3g</string>
    <string name="dijon_mustard_kiev_proteins">5g</string>
    <string name="dijon_mustard_kiev_ingredients">• 4 boneless, skinless chicken breasts\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1 cup unsalted butter, softened\n• 3 tablespoons Dijon mustard\n• 2 tablespoons fresh parsley, chopped\n• 2 cloves garlic, minced\n• 1 cup all-purpose flour\n• 2 large eggs, beaten\n• 1 cup breadcrumbs (preferably fresh or panko)\n• Olive oil for frying</string>
    <string name="dijon_mustard_kiev_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Preheat the oven to 375°F (190°C).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Season the chicken breasts with salt and black pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> In a bowl, combine softened butter, Dijon mustard, chopped parsley, and minced garlic. Mix well to create the Dijon mustard butter mixture.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Flatten each chicken breast slightly with a meat mallet.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Place a generous portion of the Dijon mustard butter in the center of each chicken breast.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Fold the sides of the chicken breast over the butter and roll it tightly, sealing the edges to form a log or cylinder shape.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Dredge each chicken breast in flour, shaking off excess.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Dip the floured chicken into the beaten eggs, ensuring it\'s fully coated.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Coat each chicken breast with breadcrumbs, pressing the crumbs onto the chicken to adhere.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Heat olive oil in a large skillet over medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 11:</b> Fry the breaded chicken until golden brown on all sides (about 2-3 minutes per side).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 12:</b> Transfer the fried chicken to a baking dish.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 13:</b> Bake in the preheated oven for 20-25 minutes or until the chicken is cooked through.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 14:</b> Serve the Dijon Mustard Chicken Kiev with a side of roasted vegetables or your favorite side dishes.]]></string>

    <string name="spinach_feta_kiev">Spinach and Feta Stuffed Chicken</string>
    <string name="spinach_feta_kiev_time">55min</string>
    <string name="spinach_feta_kiev_calories">77kcal</string>
    <string name="spinach_feta_kiev_fats">3g</string>
    <string name="spinach_feta_kiev_proteins">5g</string>
    <string name="spinach_feta_kiev_ingredients">• 4 boneless, skinless chicken breasts\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 2 cups fresh spinach, chopped\n• 1 cup feta cheese, crumbled\n• 2 cloves garlic, minced\n• 1 tablespoon olive oil\n• 1 teaspoon dried oregano\n• 1 cup all-purpose flour\n• 2 large eggs, beaten\n• 1 cup breadcrumbs (preferably fresh or panko)\n• Olive oil for frying</string>
    <string name="spinach_feta_kiev_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Preheat the oven to 375°F (190°C).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Season the chicken breasts with salt and black pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> In a skillet, heat olive oil over medium heat. Add minced garlic and sauté until fragrant.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Add chopped spinach to the skillet and cook until wilted. Remove from heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> In a bowl, combine the cooked spinach, crumbled feta cheese, and dried oregano. Mix well.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Cut a pocket into each chicken breast without cutting through the other side.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Stuff each chicken breast with the spinach and feta mixture.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Dredge each stuffed chicken breast in flour, shaking off excess.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Dip the floured chicken into the beaten eggs, ensuring it\'s fully coated.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Coat each chicken breast with breadcrumbs, pressing the crumbs onto the chicken to adhere.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 11:</b> Heat olive oil in a large skillet over medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 12:</b> Fry the breaded chicken until golden brown on all sides (about 2-3 minutes per side).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 13:</b> Transfer the fried chicken to a baking dish.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 14:</b> Bake in the preheated oven for 20-25 minutes or until the chicken is cooked through.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 15:</b> Serve the Spinach and Feta Stuffed Chicken with a side of quinoa or your favorite side dishes.]]></string>

    <!--    ##########   Chicken Salsa Recipe-->

    <string name="creamy_salsa_chicken_title">Creamy Salsa Chicken</string>
    <string name="creamy_salsa_chicken_time">45min</string>
    <string name="creamy_salsa_chicken_calories">77kcal</string>
    <string name="creamy_salsa_chicken_fats">3g</string>
    <string name="creamy_salsa_chicken_proteins">5g</string>
    <string name="creamy_salsa_chicken_ingredients">• 4 boneless, skinless chicken breasts\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1 cup salsa (homemade or store-bought)\n• 1 cup sour cream\n• 1 cup shredded cheddar cheese\n• 1 teaspoon ground cumin\n• 1 teaspoon chili powder\n• 1 teaspoon garlic powder\n• 2 tablespoons olive oil\n• Fresh cilantro, chopped (for garnish)\n• Lime wedges (for serving)</string>
    <string name="creamy_salsa_chicken_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Preheat the oven to 375°F (190°C).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Season the chicken breasts with salt, black pepper, ground cumin, chili powder, and garlic powder.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> In a skillet, heat olive oil over medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Brown the chicken breasts on both sides, about 3-4 minutes per side. Remove from the skillet and set aside.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> In the same skillet, pour in salsa and bring it to a simmer.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Return the browned chicken breasts to the skillet, coating them in the salsa.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Cover the skillet with a lid or foil and transfer it to the preheated oven.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Bake for 20-25 minutes or until the chicken is cooked through.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> In a bowl, mix sour cream with shredded cheddar cheese.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> After removing the skillet from the oven, spread the sour cream and cheese mixture over each chicken breast.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 11:</b> Broil for an additional 2-3 minutes or until the cheese is melted and bubbly.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 12:</b> Garnish with chopped fresh cilantro.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 13:</b> Serve the Creamy Salsa Chicken over rice or with your favorite side dishes.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 14:</b> Squeeze lime wedges over the chicken before serving.]]></string>

    <string name="mango_salsa_chicken_title">Mango Salsa Chicken</string>
    <string name="mango_salsa_chicken_time">50min</string>
    <string name="mango_salsa_chicken_calories">77kcal</string>
    <string name="mango_salsa_chicken_fats">3g</string>
    <string name="mango_salsa_chicken_proteins">5g</string>
    <string name="mango_salsa_chicken_ingredients">• 4 boneless, skinless chicken breasts\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1 cup mango salsa (homemade or store-bought)\n• 1 tablespoon olive oil\n• 1 teaspoon ground cumin\n• 1 teaspoon chili powder\n• 1 teaspoon garlic powder\n• Fresh cilantro, chopped (for garnish)\n• Lime wedges (for serving)1 large mango, diced\n• 1/2 red onion, finely chopped\n• 1 red bell pepper, diced\n• 1 jalapeño, seeded and minced\n• 1/4 cup fresh cilantro, chopped\n• Juice of 1 lime\n• Salt to taste</string>
    <string name="mango_salsa_chicken_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> In a bowl, combine diced mango, chopped red onion, diced red bell pepper, minced jalapeño, chopped cilantro, lime juice, and salt. Mix well and set aside<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Preheat the oven to 375°F (190°C).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Season the chicken breasts with salt, black pepper, ground cumin, chili powder, and garlic powder.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> In a skillet, heat olive oil over medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Brown the chicken breasts on both sides, about 3-4 minutes per side. Remove from the skillet and set aside.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> In the same skillet, pour in mango salsa and bring it to a simmer.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Return the browned chicken breasts to the skillet, coating them in the mango salsa.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Cover the skillet with a lid or foil and transfer it to the preheated oven.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Bake for 20-25 minutes or until the chicken is cooked through.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Garnish with fresh chopped cilantro.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 11:</b> Serve the Mango Salsa Chicken over rice or with your favorite side dishes.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 12:</b> Squeeze lime wedges over the chicken before serving.]]></string>

    <string name="green_salsa_chicken_title">Green Salsa Chicken</string>
    <string name="green_salsa_chicken_time">1hr</string>
    <string name="green_salsa_chicken_calories">77kcal</string>
    <string name="green_salsa_chicken_fats">3g</string>
    <string name="green_salsa_chicken_proteins">5g</string>
    <string name="green_salsa_chicken_ingredients">• 4 boneless, skinless chicken breasts\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1 cup green salsa (salsa verde, homemade or store-bought)\n• 1 tablespoon olive oil\n• 1 teaspoon ground cumin\n• 1 teaspoon chili powder\n• 1 teaspoon garlic powder\n• 1 cup shredded Monterey Jack or pepper jack cheese\n• Fresh cilantro, chopped (for garnish)\n• Lime wedges (for serving)</string>
    <string name="green_salsa_chicken_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Preheat the oven to 375°F (190°C).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Season the chicken breasts with salt, black pepper, ground cumin, chili powder, and garlic powder.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> In a skillet, heat olive oil over medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Brown the chicken breasts on both sides, about 3-4 minutes per side. Remove from the skillet and set aside.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> In the same skillet, pour in green salsa and bring it to a simmer.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Return the browned chicken breasts to the skillet, coating them in the green salsa.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Cover the skillet with a lid or foil and transfer it to the preheated oven.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Bake for 20-25 minutes or until the chicken is cooked through.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> In the last 5 minutes of baking, sprinkle shredded Monterey Jack or pepper jack cheese over each chicken breast.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Garnish with fresh chopped cilantro.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 11:</b> Serve the Green Salsa Chicken over rice or with your favorite side dishes.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 12:</b> Squeeze lime wedges over the chicken before serving.]]></string>

    <string name="bake_salsa_chicken_title">Salsa Chicken Bake</string>
    <string name="bake_salsa_chicken_time">1hr</string>
    <string name="bake_salsa_chicken_calories">77kcal</string>
    <string name="bake_salsa_chicken_fats">3g</string>
    <string name="bake_salsa_chicken_proteins">5g</string>
    <string name="bake_salsa_chicken_ingredients">• 4 boneless, skinless chicken breasts\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1 cup salsa (homemade or store-bought)\n• 1 cup black beans, drained and rinsed\n• 1 cup corn kernels (fresh, frozen, or canned)\n• 1 cup shredded Mexican cheese blend\n• 1 teaspoon ground cumin\n• 1 teaspoon chili powder\n• 1 teaspoon garlic powder\n• 1 tablespoon olive oil\n• Fresh cilantro, chopped (for garnish)\n• Lime wedges (for serving)</string>
    <string name="bake_salsa_chicken_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Preheat the oven to 375°F (190°C).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Season the chicken breasts with salt, black pepper, ground cumin, chili powder, and garlic powder.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> In a skillet, heat olive oil over medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Brown the chicken breasts on both sides, about 3-4 minutes per side. Remove from the skillet and set aside.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> In a baking dish, spread a thin layer of salsa on the bottom.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Place the browned chicken breasts in the baking dish.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> In a bowl, mix the remaining salsa with black beans and corn. Spoon the mixture over the chicken breasts.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Sprinkle shredded Mexican cheese blend over the top.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Cover the baking dish with foil.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Bake in the preheated oven for 20-25 minutes or until the chicken is cooked through.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 11:</b> In the last 5 minutes of baking, remove the foil to allow the cheese to melt and slightly brown.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 12:</b> Garnish with fresh chopped cilantro.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 13:</b> Serve the Salsa Chicken Bake with lime wedges.]]></string>

    <string name="verda_salsa_chicken_title">Salsa Verde Chicken</string>
    <string name="verda_salsa_chicken_time">40min</string>
    <string name="verda_salsa_chicken_calories">77kcal</string>
    <string name="verda_salsa_chicken_fats">3g</string>
    <string name="verda_salsa_chicken_proteins">5g</string>
    <string name="verda_salsa_chicken_ingredients">• 4 boneless, skinless chicken breasts\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1 cup salsa verde (homemade or store-bought)\n• 1 teaspoon ground cumin\n• 1 teaspoon chili powder\n• 1 teaspoon garlic powder\n• 1 tablespoon olive oil\n• 1 cup shredded Monterey Jack or pepper jack cheese\n• Fresh cilantro, chopped (for garnish)\n• Lime wedges (for serving)</string>
    <string name="verda_salsa_chicken_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Preheat the oven to 375°F (190°C).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Season the chicken breasts with salt, black pepper, ground cumin, chili powder, and garlic powder.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> In a skillet, heat olive oil over medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Brown the chicken breasts on both sides, about 3-4 minutes per side. Remove from the skillet and set aside.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> In the same skillet, pour in salsa verde and bring it to a simmer.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Return the browned chicken breasts to the skillet, coating them in the salsa verde.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Cover the skillet with a lid or foil and transfer it to the preheated oven.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Bake for 20-25 minutes or until the chicken is cooked through.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> In the last 5 minutes of baking, sprinkle shredded Monterey Jack or pepper jack cheese over each chicken breast.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Garnish with fresh chopped cilantro.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 11:</b> Serve the Salsa Verde Chicken over rice or with your favorite side dishes.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 12:</b> Squeeze lime wedges over the chicken before serving.]]></string>

    <string name="grilled_salsa_chicken_title">Grilled Salsa Chicken</string>
    <string name="grilled_salsa_chicken_time">35min</string>
    <string name="grilled_salsa_chicken_calories">77kcal</string>
    <string name="grilled_salsa_chicken_fats">3g</string>
    <string name="grilled_salsa_chicken_proteins">5g</string>
    <string name="grilled_salsa_chicken_ingredients">• 4 boneless, skinless chicken breasts\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1 cup salsa (homemade or store-bought)\n• 2 tablespoons olive oil\n• 1 teaspoon ground cumin\n• 1 teaspoon chili powder\n• 1 teaspoon garlic powder\n• 1 lime, juiced\n• Fresh cilantro, chopped (for garnish)</string>
    <string name="grilled_salsa_chicken_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Preheat the grill to medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Season the chicken breasts with salt, black pepper, ground cumin, chili powder, and garlic powder.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> In a bowl, mix salsa with olive oil and lime juice.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Brush both sides of the chicken breasts with the salsa mixture.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Place the chicken breasts on the preheated grill.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Grill for 6-8 minutes per side, or until the chicken is cooked through and has distinct grill marks.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> During the last few minutes of grilling, baste the chicken with additional salsa mixture.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Remove the grilled chicken from the grill and let it rest for a few minutes.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Garnish with fresh chopped cilantro.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Serve the Grilled Salsa Chicken with additional salsa on the side and your favorite grilled vegetables.]]></string>

    <string name="pineapple_salsa_chicken_title">Pineapple Salsa Chicken</string>
    <string name="pineapple_salsa_chicken_time">50min</string>
    <string name="pineapple_salsa_chicken_calories">77kcal</string>
    <string name="pineapple_salsa_chicken_fats">3g</string>
    <string name="pineapple_salsa_chicken_proteins">5g</string>
    <string name="pineapple_salsa_chicken_ingredients">• 4 boneless, skinless chicken breasts\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1 tablespoon olive oil\n• 1 teaspoon ground cumin\n• 1 teaspoon chili powder\n• 1 teaspoon garlic powder\n• 1 cup diced fresh pineapple\n• Fresh cilantro, chopped (for garnish)\n• Lime wedges (for serving)</string>
    <string name="pineapple_salsa_chicken_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Preheat the oven to 375°F (190°C).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Season the chicken breasts with salt, black pepper, ground cumin, chili powder, and garlic powder.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> In a skillet, heat olive oil over medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Brown the chicken breasts on both sides, about 3-4 minutes per side. Remove from the skillet and set aside.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> In a bowl, combine pineapple salsa with diced fresh pineapple.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> In the same skillet, pour in the pineapple salsa mixture and bring it to a simmer.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Return the browned chicken breasts to the skillet, coating them in the pineapple salsa.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Cover the skillet with a lid or foil and transfer it to the preheated oven.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Bake for 20-25 minutes or until the chicken is cooked through.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Garnish with fresh chopped cilantro.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 11:</b> Serve the Pineapple Salsa Chicken over rice or with your favorite side dishes.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 12:</b> Squeeze lime wedges over the chicken before serving.]]></string>

    <string name="mexican_salsa_chicken_title">Mexican Salsa Chicken</string>
    <string name="mexican_salsa_chicken_time">45min</string>
    <string name="mexican_salsa_chicken_calories">77kcal</string>
    <string name="mexican_salsa_chicken_fats">3g</string>
    <string name="mexican_salsa_chicken_proteins">5g</string>
    <string name="mexican_salsa_chicken_ingredients">• 4 boneless, skinless chicken breasts\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1 cup Mexican salsa (homemade or store-bought)\n• 1 tablespoon olive oil\n• 1 teaspoon ground cumin\n• 1 teaspoon chili powder\n• 1 teaspoon garlic powder\n• 1 cup shredded Mexican cheese blend\n• Fresh cilantro, chopped (for garnish)\n• Lime wedges (for serving)\n• Optional toppings: diced tomatoes, sliced jalapeños, sour cream</string>
    <string name="mexican_salsa_chicken_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Preheat the oven to 375°F (190°C).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Season the chicken breasts with salt, black pepper, ground cumin, chili powder, and garlic powder.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> In a skillet, heat olive oil over medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Brown the chicken breasts on both sides, about 3-4 minutes per side. Remove from the skillet and set aside.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> In the same skillet, pour in Mexican salsa and bring it to a simmer.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Return the browned chicken breasts to the skillet, coating them in the Mexican salsa.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Cover the skillet with a lid or foil and transfer it to the preheated oven.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Bake for 20-25 minutes or until the chicken is cooked through.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> In the last 5 minutes of baking, sprinkle shredded Mexican cheese blend over each chicken breast.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Garnish with fresh chopped cilantro.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 11:</b> Serve the Mexican Salsa Chicken over rice or with your favorite side dishes.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 12:</b> Squeeze lime wedges over the chicken before serving.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 13:</b> Optional: Top with diced tomatoes, sliced jalapeños, and a dollop of sour cream.]]></string>

    <string name="bbq_salsa_chicken_title">BBQ Salsa Chicken</string>
    <string name="bbq_salsa_chicken_time">45min</string>
    <string name="bbq_salsa_chicken_calories">77kcal</string>
    <string name="bbq_salsa_chicken_fats">3g</string>
    <string name="bbq_salsa_chicken_proteins">5g</string>
    <string name="bbq_salsa_chicken_ingredients">• 4 boneless, skinless chicken breasts\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1 cup barbecue sauce (homemade or store-bought)\n• 1 cup salsa (homemade or store-bought)\n• 1 tablespoon olive oil\n• 1 teaspoon smoked paprika\n• 1 teaspoon garlic powder\n• 1 teaspoon onion powder\n• 1 cup shredded cheddar cheese\n• Green onions, sliced (for garnish)\n• Jalapeño slices (for garnish, optional)</string>
    <string name="bbq_salsa_chicken_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Preheat the oven to 375°F (190°C).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Season the chicken breasts with salt, black pepper, smoked paprika, garlic powder, and onion powder.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> In a skillet, heat olive oil over medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Brown the chicken breasts on both sides, about 3-4 minutes per side. Remove from the skillet and set aside.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> In a bowl, mix barbecue sauce with salsa.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> In the same skillet, pour in the barbecue and salsa mixture. Bring it to a simmer.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Return the browned chicken breasts to the skillet, coating them in the BBQ salsa mixture.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Cover the skillet with a lid or foil and transfer it to the preheated oven.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Bake for 20-25 minutes or until the chicken is cooked through.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> In the last 5 minutes of baking, sprinkle shredded cheddar cheese over each chicken breast.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 11:</b> Garnish with sliced green onions and jalapeño slices (optional).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 12:</b> Serve the BBQ Salsa Chicken over rice or with your favorite side dishes.]]></string>

    <string name="buffalo_salsa_chicken_title">Buffalo Salsa Chicken</string>
    <string name="buffalo_salsa_chicken_time">50min</string>
    <string name="buffalo_salsa_chicken_calories">77kcal</string>
    <string name="buffalo_salsa_chicken_fats">3g</string>
    <string name="buffalo_salsa_chicken_proteins">5g</string>
    <string name="buffalo_salsa_chicken_ingredients">• 4 boneless, skinless chicken breasts\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1 cup buffalo sauce\n• 1 cup salsa (homemade or store-bought)\n• 2 tablespoons olive oil\n• 1 teaspoon garlic powder\n• 1 teaspoon onion powder\n• 1 teaspoon smoked paprika\n• Blue cheese crumbles (for garnish\n• Celery sticks (for serving)</string>
    <string name="buffalo_salsa_chicken_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Preheat the oven to 375°F (190°C).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Season the chicken breasts with salt, black pepper, garlic powder, onion powder, and smoked paprika.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> In a skillet, heat olive oil over medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Brown the chicken breasts on both sides, about 3-4 minutes per side. Remove from the skillet and set aside.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> In a bowl, mix buffalo sauce with salsa.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> In the same skillet, pour in the buffalo and salsa mixture. Bring it to a simmer.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Return the browned chicken breasts to the skillet, coating them in the buffalo salsa.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Cover the skillet with a lid or foil and transfer it to the preheated oven.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Bake for 20-25 minutes or until the chicken is cooked through.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Garnish with blue cheese crumbles.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 11:</b> Serve the Buffalo Salsa Chicken with celery sticks on the side.]]></string>

    <!--    ##########   Spice Chicken Recipe-->

    <string name="spicy_chicken_spicy_title">Spicy Chicken Curry</string>
    <string name="spicy_chicken_spicy_time">1hr</string>
    <string name="spicy_chicken_spicy_calories">77kcal</string>
    <string name="spicy_chicken_spicy_fats">3g</string>
    <string name="spicy_chicken_spicy_proteins">5g</string>
    <string name="spicy_chicken_spicy_ingredients">• 1.5 lbs (680g) boneless, skinless chicken thighs, cut into bite-sized pieces\n• 2 large onions, finely chopped\n• 3 tomatoes, chopped\n• 1/4 cup vegetable oil\n• 3 cloves garlic, minced\n• 1-inch piece of ginger, grated\n• 2 green chilies, finely chopped\n• 1 cup coconut milk\n• 1/2 cup plain yogurt\n• 2 tablespoons curry powder\n• 1 tablespoon garam masala\n• 1 tablespoon ground coriander\n• 1 teaspoon turmeric\n• 1 teaspoon cumin\n• 1/2 teaspoon cayenne pepper (adjust to taste for desired spice level)\n• Salt to taste\n• Fresh cilantro, chopped (for garnish)\n•Cooked basmati rice or naan bread (for serving)</string>
    <string name="spicy_chicken_spicy_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> In a large pan or pot, heat the vegetable oil over medium heat. Add chopped onions and cook until they become golden brown.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Add minced garlic, grated ginger, and chopped green chilies. Sauté for 2-3 minutes until fragrant.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Add curry powder, garam masala, ground coriander, turmeric, cumin, and cayenne pepper. Stir well to coat the onions with the spices.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Add chopped tomatoes and cook until they soften and the oil starts to separate from the spice mixture.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Add the bite-sized chicken pieces to the pan. Cook until the chicken is browned on all sides.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Pour in the coconut milk and plain yogurt. Stir to combine.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Reduce the heat to low, cover the pan, and let the curry simmer for 20-25 minutes, or until the chicken is cooked through and tender.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Season with salt to taste.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Garnish with chopped cilantro.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Serve the Spicy Chicken Curry over cooked basmati rice or with naan bread.]]></string>

    <string name="spicy_garlic_spicy_title">Spicy Garlic Lime Chicken</string>
    <string name="spicy_garlic_spicy_time">40min</string>
    <string name="spicy_garlic_spicy_calories">77kcal</string>
    <string name="spicy_garlic_spicy_fats">3g</string>
    <string name="spicy_garlic_spicy_proteins">5g</string>
    <string name="spicy_garlic_spicy_ingredients">• 4 boneless, skinless chicken breasts\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 4 cloves garlic, minced\n• Zest and juice of 2 limes\n• 2 tablespoons olive oil\n• 1 teaspoon ground cumin\n• 1 teaspoon chili powder\n• 1 teaspoon paprika\n• 1/2 teaspoon cayenne pepper (adjust to taste)\n• 2 tablespoons chopped fresh cilantro\n• Lime wedges (for serving)\n• Sliced green onions (for garnish)\n• Cooked rice or quinoa (for serving)</string>
    <string name="spicy_garlic_spicy_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Preheat the oven to 400°F (200°C).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Season the chicken breasts with salt and black pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> In a bowl, mix minced garlic, lime zest, lime juice, olive oil, ground cumin, chili powder, paprika, and cayenne pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Place the chicken breasts in a baking dish.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Pour the garlic lime marinade over the chicken, ensuring each piece is well coated.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Let the chicken marinate for at least 15 minutes.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Bake in the preheated oven for 20-25 minutes or until the chicken is cooked through.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Sprinkle chopped cilantro over the cooked chicken.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Serve the Spicy Garlic Lime Chicken over cooked rice or quinoa.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Garnish with lime wedges and sliced green onions.]]></string>

    <string name="buffalo_spicy_title">Buffalo Chicken Wings</string>
    <string name="buffalo_spicy_time">1hr</string>
    <string name="buffalo_spicy_calories">77kcal</string>
    <string name="buffalo_spicy_fats">3g</string>
    <string name="buffalo_spicy_proteins">5g</string>
    <string name="buffalo_spicy_ingredients">• 2 lbs (about 1 kg) chicken wings, split at joints, tips discarded\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1 cup all-purpose flour\n• 1 teaspoon garlic powder\n• 1 teaspoon onion powder\n• 1/2 cup unsalted butter\n• 1/2 cup hot sauce (like Frank\'s RedHot)\n• 1/2 teaspoon Worcestershire sauce\n• Celery sticks and ranch or blue cheese dressing (for serving)</string>
    <string name="buffalo_spicy_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Preheat the oven to 400°F (200°C).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Season the chicken wings with salt and black pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> In a large bowl, combine flour, garlic powder, and onion powder. Dredge the chicken wings in the flour mixture, shaking off any excess.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Place a wire rack on a baking sheet. Arrange the coated wings on the rack.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Bake in the preheated oven for 45-50 minutes or until the wings are golden and crispy.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> While the wings are baking, prepare the buffalo sauce. In a saucepan over medium heat, melt the butter.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Stir in the hot sauce and Worcestershire sauce. Simmer for a few minutes until the sauce is well combined and heated through.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Once the wings are done baking, transfer them to a large bowl.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Pour the buffalo sauce over the wings and toss until they are evenly coated.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Serve the Buffalo Chicken Wings with celery sticks and your choice of ranch or blue cheese dressing.]]></string>

    <string name="orange_spicy_title">Spicy Orange Chicken</string>
    <string name="orange_spicy_time">35min</string>
    <string name="orange_spicy_calories">77kcal</string>
    <string name="orange_spicy_fats">3g</string>
    <string name="orange_spicy_proteins">5g</string>
    <string name="orange_spicy_ingredients">• 1.5 lbs (680g) boneless, skinless chicken thighs, cut into bite-sized pieces\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1 cup orange juice (freshly squeezed or store-bought)\n• Zest of 1 orange\n• Zest of 1 orange\n• 1/4 cup soy sauce\n• 2 tablespoons rice vinegar\n• 2 tablespoons honey\n• 1 tablespoon Sriracha sauce (adjust to taste for desired spice level)\n• 1 teaspoon sesame oil\n• 2 tablespoons cornstarch\n• 2 tablespoons vegetable oil\n• 4 green onions, sliced\n• Sesame seeds (for garnish)\n• Cooked white rice (for serving)</string>
    <string name="orange_spicy_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Season the chicken pieces with salt and black pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> In a bowl, whisk together orange juice, orange zest, soy sauce, rice vinegar, honey, Sriracha sauce, sesame oil, and cornstarch. Ensure the cornstarch is fully dissolved.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Heat vegetable oil in a large skillet or wok over medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Add the seasoned chicken to the skillet and cook until browned on all sides and cooked through. Remove the chicken from the skillet and set aside.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> In the same skillet, pour in the orange sauce mixture. Bring it to a simmer and cook until the sauce thickens.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Return the cooked chicken to the skillet, tossing to coat each piece in the spicy orange sauce.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Cook for an additional 2-3 minutes, allowing the flavors to meld.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Garnish with sliced green onions and sesame seeds.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Serve the Spicy Orange Chicken over cooked white rice.]]></string>

    <string name="satay_spicy_title">Spicy Chicken Satay</string>
    <string name="satay_spicy_time">42min</string>
    <string name="satay_spicy_calories">77kcal</string>
    <string name="satay_spicy_fats">3g</string>
    <string name="satay_spicy_proteins">5g</string>
    <string name="satay_spicy_ingredients">• 1.5 lbs (680g) boneless, skinless chicken thighs, cut into thin strips\n• 1 tablespoon soy sauce\n• 1 tablespoon fish sauce\n• 1 tablespoon curry powder\n• 1 tablespoon honey\n• 2 cloves garlic, minced\n• 1 tablespoon vegetable oil\n• Wooden skewers, soaked in water for at least 30 minutes\n• 1/2 cup creamy peanut butter\n• 3 tablespoons soy sauce\n• 2 tablespoons rice vinegar\n• 1 tablespoon honey\n• 1 tablespoon Sriracha sauce (adjust to taste)\n• 1 teaspoon sesame oil\n• 1 clove garlic, minced\n• Water (as needed to thin the sauce)</string>
    <string name="satay_spicy_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> In a bowl, mix soy sauce, fish sauce, curry powder, honey, minced garlic, and vegetable oil. Add the chicken strips and marinate for at least 30 minutes.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Preheat the grill or grill pan over medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Thread the marinated chicken strips onto the soaked wooden skewers.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Grill the chicken skewers for 4-5 minutes on each side or until fully cooked and slightly charred.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> While the chicken is grilling, prepare the spicy peanut sauce. In a bowl, whisk together peanut butter, soy sauce, rice vinegar, honey, Sriracha sauce, sesame oil, and minced garlic. Add water as needed to achieve your desired consistency.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Once the chicken skewers are done, serve them with the spicy peanut sauce on the side for dipping.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Garnish with chopped cilantro or crushed peanuts if desired.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Enjoy the Spicy Chicken Satay as an appetizer or main course.]]></string>

    <string name="firecracker_spicy_title">Firecracker Chicken</string>
    <string name="firecracker_spicy_time">40min</string>
    <string name="firecracker_spicy_calories">77kcal</string>
    <string name="firecracker_spicy_fats">3g</string>
    <string name="firecracker_spicy_proteins">5g</string>
    <string name="firecracker_spicy_ingredients">• 1.5 lbs (680g) boneless, skinless chicken breasts, cut into bite-sized pieces\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1 cup cornstarch\n• 2 large eggs, beaten\n• Vegetable oil for frying\n• 1/2 cup hot sauce (like Frank\'s RedHot)\n• 1/2 cup honey\n• 1/4 cup soy sauce\n• 2 tablespoons rice vinegar\n• 1 teaspoon minced garlic\n• 1 teaspoon minced ginger\n• 1 tablespoon cornstarch mixed with 2 tablespoons water (cornstarch slurry)\n• Sesame seeds\n• Sliced green onions\n• Cooked white rice</string>
    <string name="firecracker_spicy_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Season the chicken pieces with salt and black pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Dredge the chicken pieces in cornstarch, then dip them into beaten eggs, coating them evenly.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> In a large skillet or wok, heat vegetable oil over medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Fry the coated chicken pieces in batches until they are golden brown and cooked through. Drain on paper towels.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> In a small saucepan, combine hot sauce, honey, soy sauce, rice vinegar, minced garlic, and minced ginger. Bring the mixture to a simmer.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> In a small bowl, mix cornstarch with water to create a slurry. Add the slurry to the saucepan and stir until the sauce thickens.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Toss the fried chicken pieces in the firecracker sauce until they are fully coated.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Garnish with sesame seeds and sliced green onions.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Serve the Firecracker Chicken over cooked white rice.]]></string>

    <string name="coconut_spicy_title">Spicy Coconut Chicken Curry</string>
    <string name="coconut_spicy_time">55min</string>
    <string name="coconut_spicy_calories">77kcal</string>
    <string name="coconut_spicy_fats">3g</string>
    <string name="coconut_spicy_proteins">5g</string>
    <string name="coconut_spicy_ingredients">• 1.5 lbs (680g) boneless, skinless chicken thighs, cut into bite-sized pieces\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 2 tablespoons vegetable oil\n• 1 large onion, finely chopped\n• 3 cloves garlic, minced\n• 1 tablespoon ginger, grated\n• 2 tablespoons red curry paste\n• 1 teaspoon ground turmeric\n• 1 teaspoon ground coriander\n• 1 teaspoon chili powder (adjust to taste)\n• 1 can (14 oz) coconut milk\n• 1 cup chicken broth\n• 1 tablespoon fish sauce\n• 1 tablespoon soy sauce\n• 1 tablespoon brown sugar\n• Juice of 1 lime\n• Fresh cilantro, chopped (for garnish)\n• Fresh cilantro, chopped (for garnish)</string>
    <string name="coconut_spicy_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Season the chicken pieces with salt and black pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> In a large skillet or pot, heat vegetable oil over medium heat. Add chopped onion and cook until softened.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Add minced garlic and grated ginger to the skillet. Sauté for 2-3 minutes until fragrant.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Stir in red curry paste, ground turmeric, ground coriander, and chili powder. Cook for an additional 2 minutes.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Add the chicken pieces to the skillet, cooking until browned on all sides.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Pour in coconut milk, chicken broth, fish sauce, soy sauce, and brown sugar. Stir to combine.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Bring the mixture to a simmer and let it cook for 20-25 minutes or until the chicken is cooked through.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Just before serving, squeeze lime juice into the curry and stir.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Garnish with chopped cilantro.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Serve the Spicy Coconut Chicken Curry over cooked jasmine rice.]]></string>

    <string name="chili_spicy_title">Chili Lime Chicken</string>
    <string name="chili_spicy_time">40min</string>
    <string name="chili_spicy_calories">77kcal</string>
    <string name="chili_spicy_fats">3g</string>
    <string name="chili_spicy_proteins">5g</string>
    <string name="chili_spicy_ingredients">• 1.5 lbs (680g) boneless, skinless chicken breasts, thinly sliced\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 2 tablespoons olive oil\n• 3 tablespoons fresh lime juice\n• 2 teaspoons chili powder\n• 1 teaspoon ground cumin\n• 1 teaspoon paprika\n• 1 teaspoon garlic powder\n• 1 teaspoon onion powder\n• 1/2 teaspoon cayenne pepper (adjust to taste)\n• Fresh cilantro, chopped (for garnish)\n• Lime wedges</string>
    <string name="chili_spicy_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> In a bowl, combine olive oil, fresh lime juice, chili powder, ground cumin, paprika, garlic powder, onion powder, cayenne pepper, salt, and black pepper. Mix well.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Season the thinly sliced chicken breasts with the prepared marinade. Ensure the chicken is well-coated. Let it marinate for at least 30 minutes.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Heat a grill or grill pan over medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Grill the marinated chicken slices for 3-4 minutes per side or until fully cooked and grill marks appear.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Grill the marinated chicken slices for 3-4 minutes per side or until fully cooked and grill marks appear.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Serve the Chili Lime Chicken with lime wedges on the side.]]></string>

    <string name="harissa_spicy_title">Harissa Chicken</string>
    <string name="harissa_spicy_time">1.5 to 2hr</string>
    <string name="harissa_spicy_calories">77kcal</string>
    <string name="harissa_spicy_fats">3g</string>
    <string name="harissa_spicy_proteins">5g</string>
    <string name="harissa_spicy_ingredients">• 1.5 lbs (680g) boneless, skinless chicken thighs\n• 2 tablespoons harissa paste\n• 2 tablespoons olive oil\n• 1 teaspoon ground cumin\n• 1 teaspoon ground coriander\n• 1 teaspoon smoked paprika\n• 1 teaspoon garlic powder\n• 1 teaspoon honey\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• Fresh cilantro, chopped\n• Lemon wedges</string>
    <string name="harissa_spicy_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> In a bowl, combine harissa paste, olive oil, ground cumin, ground coriander, smoked paprika, garlic powder, honey, salt, and black pepper. Mix well to form the harissa marinade.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Pat the chicken thighs dry and place them in a resealable plastic bag or shallow dish.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Pour the harissa marinade over the chicken, ensuring each piece is well-coated. Seal the bag or cover the dish and refrigerate for at least 1 hour, or preferably overnight.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Preheat the oven to 400°F (200°C).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Remove the marinated chicken from the refrigerator and let it come to room temperature.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Transfer the chicken to a baking dish.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Bake in the preheated oven for 25-30 minutes or until the chicken is cooked through and has a nice char.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Garnish with chopped cilantro and serve with lemon wedges on the side.]]></string>

    <string name="peri_spicy_title">Peri-Peri Chicken</string>
    <string name="peri_spicy_time">2.5 to 3hr</string>
    <string name="peri_spicy_calories">77kcal</string>
    <string name="peri_spicy_fats">3g</string>
    <string name="peri_spicy_proteins">5g</string>
    <string name="peri_spicy_ingredients">• 1.5 lbs (680g) chicken drumsticks and thighs\n• 3 tablespoons olive oil\n• 3 tablespoons red wine vinegar\n• 2 cloves garlic, minced\n• 1 tablespoon smoked paprika\n• 1 tablespoon sweet paprika\n• 1 teaspoon dried oregano\n• 1 teaspoon cayenne pepper (adjust to taste)\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• Fresh parsley, chopped\n• Lemon wedges</string>
    <string name="peri_spicy_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> In a bowl, combine olive oil, red wine vinegar, minced garlic, smoked paprika, sweet paprika, dried oregano, cayenne pepper, salt, and black pepper. Mix well to create the peri-peri marinade.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Pat the chicken pieces dry and place them in a resealable plastic bag or shallow dish.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Pour the peri-peri marinade over the chicken, ensuring each piece is well-coated. Seal the bag or cover the dish and refrigerate for at least 2 hours, or preferably overnight.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Preheat the grill to medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Remove the marinated chicken from the refrigerator and let it come to room temperature.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Grill the chicken pieces for 20-25 minutes, turning occasionally, or until the chicken is fully cooked and has a nice char.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Garnish with chopped fresh parsley and serve with lemon wedges on the side.]]></string>

    <!--    ##########   Stuffed Chicken BreastsRecipe-->

    <string name="asparagus_breasts_title">Asparagus Stuffed Chicken Breasts</string>
    <string name="asparagus_breasts_time">50min</string>
    <string name="asparagus_breasts_calories">77kcal</string>
    <string name="asparagus_breasts_fats">3g</string>
    <string name="asparagus_breasts_proteins">5g</string>
    <string name="asparagus_breasts_ingredients">• 4 boneless, skinless chicken breasts\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1 tablespoon olive oil\n• 1 teaspoon garlic powder\n• 1 teaspoon paprika\n• 1/2 teaspoon dried thyme\n• 1 bunch asparagus spears, trimmed\n• 1 tablespoon olive oil\n• 2 cloves garlic, minced\n• Zest of 1 lemon\n• Zest of 1 lemon\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1/2 cup heavy cream\n• 1/4 cup grated Parmesan cheese\n• 1 tablespoon Dijon mustard\n• Salt and black pepper to taste</string>
    <string name="asparagus_breasts_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Preheat the oven to 375°F (190°C).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Season each chicken breast with salt, black pepper, garlic powder, paprika, and dried thyme.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Lay the chicken breasts flat and make a horizontal cut through the center to create a pocket for the filling.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> Toss asparagus spears with olive oil, minced garlic, lemon zest, salt, and black pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Stuff each chicken breast with the seasoned asparagus spears.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Heat olive oil in an oven-safe skillet over medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Sear the stuffed chicken breasts for 2-3 minutes on each side until they develop a golden-brown crust.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Transfer the skillet to the preheated oven and bake for 20-25 minutes or until the chicken is cooked through.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> In a small saucepan, heat heavy cream, Parmesan cheese, Dijon mustard, salt, and black pepper over low heat. Stir until the sauce is smooth and warmed through.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Drizzle the creamy Parmesan sauce over the stuffed chicken breasts before serving.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 11:</b> Garnish with additional fresh thyme or chopped parsley if desired.]]></string>

    <string name="caprese_breasts_title">Caprese Stuffed Chicken Breast</string>
    <string name="caprese_breasts_time">45min</string>
    <string name="caprese_breasts_calories">77kcal</string>
    <string name="caprese_breasts_fats">3g</string>
    <string name="caprese_breasts_proteins">5g</string>
    <string name="caprese_breasts_ingredients">• 4 boneless, skinless chicken breasts\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1 tablespoon olive oil\n• 1 teaspoon garlic powder\n• 1 teaspoon dried oregano\n• 1 teaspoon dried basil\n• 1 cup cherry tomatoes, halved\n• 1 cup fresh mozzarella, diced\n• 1/4 cup fresh basil leaves, chopped\n• Balsamic glaze (for drizzling)</string>
    <string name="caprese_breasts_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Preheat the oven to 375°F (190°C).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Season each chicken breast with salt, black pepper, garlic powder, dried oregano, and dried basil.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Lay the chicken breasts flat and make a horizontal cut through the center to create a pocket for the filling.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> In a bowl, combine cherry tomatoes, fresh mozzarella, and chopped basil.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Stuff each chicken breast with the Caprese filling mixture.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Heat olive oil in an oven-safe skillet over medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Sear the stuffed chicken breasts for 2-3 minutes on each side until they develop a golden-brown crust.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Transfer the skillet to the preheated oven and bake for 20-25 minutes or until the chicken is cooked through.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Drizzle with balsamic glaze before serving.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Garnish with additional fresh basil leaves if desired.]]></string>

    <string name="spinach_breasts_title">Spinach Stuffed Chicken Breast</string>
    <string name="spinach_breasts_time">35min</string>
    <string name="spinach_breasts_calories">77kcal</string>
    <string name="spinach_breasts_fats">3g</string>
    <string name="spinach_breasts_proteins">5g</string>
    <string name="spinach_breasts_ingredients">• 4 boneless, skinless chicken breasts\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1 tablespoon olive oil\n• 1 teaspoon garlic powder\n• 1 teaspoon onion powder\n• 1 teaspoon paprika\n• 2 cups fresh spinach, chopped\n• 1/2 cup feta cheese, crumbled\n• 1/4 cup sun-dried tomatoes, chopped\n• 2 cloves garlic, minced\n• Salt and black pepper to taste</string>
    <string name="spinach_breasts_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Preheat the oven to 375°F (190°C).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Season each chicken breast with salt, black pepper, garlic powder, onion powder, and paprika.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Lay the chicken breasts flat and make a horizontal cut through the center to create a pocket for the filling.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> In a bowl, combine chopped spinach, crumbled feta cheese, chopped sun-dried tomatoes, minced garlic, salt, and black pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Stuff each chicken breast with the spinach filling mixture.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Heat olive oil in an oven-safe skillet over medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Sear the stuffed chicken breasts for 2-3 minutes on each side until they develop a golden-brown crust.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Transfer the skillet to the preheated oven and bake for 20-25 minutes or until the chicken is cooked through.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Garnish with additional fresh spinach or herbs if desired.]]></string>

    <string name="cheddar_breasts_title">Cheddar Stuffed Chicken Breast</string>
    <string name="cheddar_breasts_time">40min</string>
    <string name="cheddar_breasts_calories">77kcal</string>
    <string name="cheddar_breasts_fats">3g</string>
    <string name="cheddar_breasts_proteins">5g</string>
    <string name="cheddar_breasts_ingredients">• 4 boneless, skinless chicken breasts\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1 tablespoon olive oil\n• 1 teaspoon garlic powder\n• 1 teaspoon smoked paprika\n• 1 cup sharp cheddar cheese, shredded\n• 1/4 cup green onions, finely chopped\n• 1/4 cup cream cheese, softened\n• 1 teaspoon Dijon mustard\n• Salt and black pepper to taste</string>
    <string name="cheddar_breasts_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Preheat the oven to 375°F (190°C).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Season each chicken breast with salt, black pepper, garlic powder, and smoked paprika.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Lay the chicken breasts flat and make a horizontal cut through the center to create a pocket for the filling.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> In a bowl, combine shredded sharp cheddar cheese, chopped green onions, softened cream cheese, Dijon mustard, salt, and black pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Stuff each chicken breast with the cheddar filling mixture.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Heat olive oil in an oven-safe skillet over medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Sear the stuffed chicken breasts for 2-3 minutes on each side until they develop a golden-brown crust.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Transfer the skillet to the preheated oven and bake for 20-25 minutes or until the chicken is cooked through.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Garnish with additional green onions if desired.]]></string>

    <string name="mushroom_breasts_title">Mushroom Stuffed Chicken Breast</string>
    <string name="mushroom_breasts_time">50min</string>
    <string name="mushroom_breasts_calories">77kcal</string>
    <string name="mushroom_breasts_fats">3g</string>
    <string name="mushroom_breasts_proteins">5g</string>
    <string name="mushroom_breasts_ingredients">• 4 boneless, skinless chicken breasts\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1 tablespoon olive oil\n• 1 teaspoon garlic powder\n• 1 teaspoon dried thyme\n• 1 cup mushrooms, finely chopped\n• 1 cup Swiss cheese, shredded\n• 2 tablespoons butter\n• 2 cloves garlic, minced\n• 1/4 cup fresh parsley, chopped\n• Salt and black pepper to taste</string>
    <string name="mushroom_breasts_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Preheat the oven to 375°F (190°C).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Season each chicken breast with salt, black pepper, garlic powder, and dried thyme.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Lay the chicken breasts flat and make a horizontal cut through the center to create a pocket for the filling.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> In a skillet, melt butter over medium heat. Add chopped mushrooms and minced garlic. Cook until the mushrooms are softened.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Remove the skillet from heat and stir in shredded Swiss cheese and chopped fresh parsley. Season with salt and black pepper to taste.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Stuff each chicken breast with the mushroom and Swiss filling mixture.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Heat olive oil in an oven-safe skillet over medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Sear the stuffed chicken breasts for 2-3 minutes on each side until they develop a golden-brown crust.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Transfer the skillet to the preheated oven and bake for 20-25 minutes or until the chicken is cooked through.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 10:</b> Garnish with additional fresh parsley if desired.]]></string>

    <string name="cheese_breasts_title">Cheese Stuffed Chicken Breast</string>
    <string name="cheese_breasts_time">45min</string>
    <string name="cheese_breasts_calories">77kcal</string>
    <string name="cheese_breasts_fats">3g</string>
    <string name="cheese_breasts_proteins">5g</string>
    <string name="cheese_breasts_ingredients">• 4 boneless, skinless chicken breasts\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1 tablespoon olive oil\n• 1 teaspoon garlic powder\n• 1 teaspoon Italian seasoning (optional)\n• 1 cup mixed cheeses (cheddar, mozzarella, and Parmesan), shredded\n• 1/4 cup cream cheese, softened\n• 2 tablespoons fresh herbs (such as parsley or chives), chopped\n• Salt and black pepper to taste</string>
    <string name="cheese_breasts_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Preheat the oven to 375°F (190°C).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Season each chicken breast with salt, black pepper, garlic powder, and Italian seasoning.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Lay the chicken breasts flat and make a horizontal cut through the center to create a pocket for the filling.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> In a bowl, combine shredded mixed cheeses, softened cream cheese, chopped fresh herbs, salt, and black pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Stuff each chicken breast with the cheese filling mixture.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Heat olive oil in an oven-safe skillet over medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Sear the stuffed chicken breasts for 2-3 minutes on each side until they develop a golden-brown crust.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Transfer the skillet to the preheated oven and bake for 20-25 minutes or until the chicken is cooked through.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Garnish with additional fresh herbs if desired.]]></string>

    <string name="mozzarella_breasts_title"> Mozzarella Stuffed Chicken Breast</string>
    <string name="mozzarella_breasts_time">35min</string>
    <string name="mozzarella_breasts_calories">77kcal</string>
    <string name="mozzarella_breasts_fats">3g</string>
    <string name="mozzarella_breasts_proteins">5g</string>
    <string name="mozzarella_breasts_ingredients">• 4 boneless, skinless chicken breasts\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1 tablespoon olive oil\n• 1 teaspoon garlic powder\n• 1 teaspoon dried basil\n• 1/2 teaspoon dried oregano\n• 1 cup mozzarella cheese, shredded\n• 1/4 cup sun-dried tomatoes, chopped\n• 2 tablespoons fresh basil leaves, chopped\n• Salt and black pepper to taste</string>
    <string name="mozzarella_breasts_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Preheat the oven to 375°F (190°C).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Season each chicken breast with salt, black pepper, garlic powder, dried basil, and dried oregano.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> Lay the chicken breasts flat and make a horizontal cut through the center to create a pocket for the filling.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b> In a bowl, combine shredded mozzarella cheese, chopped sun-dried tomatoes, chopped fresh basil, salt, and black pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Stuff each chicken breast with the mozzarella filling mixture.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Heat olive oil in an oven-safe skillet over medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Sear the stuffed chicken breasts for 2-3 minutes on each side until they develop a golden-brown crust.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Transfer the skillet to the preheated oven and bake for 20-25 minutes or until the chicken is cooked through.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Garnish with additional fresh basil if desired.]]></string>

    <string name="parmesan_breasts_title">Parmesan Stuffed Chicken Breast</string>
    <string name="parmesan_breasts_time">1hr</string>
    <string name="parmesan_breasts_calories">77kcal</string>
    <string name="parmesan_breasts_fats">3g</string>
    <string name="parmesan_breasts_proteins">5g</string>
    <string name="parmesan_breasts_ingredients">• 4 boneless, skinless chicken breasts\n• Salt and black pepper to taste\n• 1 tablespoon olive oil\n• 1 teaspoon garlic powder\n• 1 teaspoon dried thyme\n• 1 cup Parmesan cheese, grated\n• 1/4 cup cream cheese, softened\n• 2 tablespoons fresh parsley, chopped\n• Zest of 1 lemon\n• Salt and black pepper to taste</string>
    <string name="parmesan_breasts_instruction"><![CDATA[
        <b>Step 1:</b> Preheat the oven to 375°F (190°C).<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 2:</b> Lay the chicken breasts flat and make a horizontal cut through the center to create a pocket for the filling.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 3:</b> In a bowl, combine grated Parmesan cheese, softened cream cheese, chopped fresh parsley, lemon zest, salt, and black pepper.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 4:</b>In a bowl, combine grated Parmesan cheese, softened cream cheese, chopped fresh parsley, lemon zest, salt, and black pepper. <br/><br/>
        <b>Step 5:</b> Stuff each chicken breast with the Parmesan filling mixture.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 6:</b> Heat olive oil in an oven-safe skillet over medium-high heat.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 7:</b> Sear the stuffed chicken breasts for 2-3 minutes on each side until they develop a golden-brown crust.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 8:</b> Transfer the skillet to the preheated oven and bake for 20-25 minutes or until the chicken is cooked through.<br/><br/>
        <b>Step 9:</b> Garnish with additional fresh parsley if desired.]]></string>


</resources>